...and then what do you put in?<P><END>
You put in... ...then you use the...<P><END>
I never would have thought of that!...<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. Come on in.<P><END>
Hi there, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
What were we doing? Anna was just teaching me how to make desserts.<P><C>
She's famous for her desserts, you know.<P><END>
Oh, stop flattering me, Manna!...<P><END>
It's true! You cook too, don't you, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><C>
In that case, you should learn from Anna, too!<P><END>
Learn.<END>
Sorry, I'm too busy.<END>
Really? I'd be glad to teach you!<P><END>
In that case, both of you listen to this simple and easy Cake recipe.<P><C>
Ingredients are Eggs, Flour, and Butter.<P><C>
Seasoning is Sugar, of course. First, mix the Egg and <WB>
Butter with a Whisk, then add Flour and put it all in the Oven.<P><C>
Not too hard, is it? You can also add all kinds of fruit to make it even <WB>
better. Or, you can add Chocolate to make it a Chocolate Cake!<P><END>
Can you teach me anything else?<P><END>
How about this... Come back again at this same time and I'll teach you a <WB>
new dish.<P><C>
It'll be a miniature cooking school!<P><END>
Really? That sounds great!<P><END>
Sure! I'd love to!<P><END>
You'll come too, won't you <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
Aww...You're no fun! Don't you know that women love a man who knows<WB>
how to cook?<P><END>
I'm sure he's busy, Manna. It's tough running a farm all by yourself, after all!<P><C>
I'll teach you, instead.<P><END>
How about a recipe for a Cake, then? Duke loves Cake...<P><END>
OK. First you...<P><END>
