It's me. How are you?<P><END>
You're not ready to come back yet...?<P><C>
...I see.<P><C>
I'll call again. Take care.<P><END>
Was that Joanna?<P><END>
..Yes...<P><C>
May waits everyday for her to come home, <WB>
but she won't...!<P><END>
I bet she has her reasons.<P><END>
Could there be anything more important than her own daughter?!<P><C>
Poor May...<P><END>
I remember... She was away for a long time, and when she finally <WB>
did come back home she left May with you and then took off again!<P><END>
Joanna's always been that way.<P><C>
She tries to solve all her problems by herself.<P><END>
I can't forgive her this time, though!<P><C>
Leaving May with me and going off to the city... all without telling me why!<P><C>
May tries to act brave, but she misses her mother.<P><C>
It makes me so mad...!!<P><END>
She's still at that age where she needs her mom, isn't she...?<P><END>
Joanna keeps insisting she has more business to take care of...<P><C>
What could it be!?<P><END>
I'll make May's favorite today. Bye now.<P><END>
