Hmm....<P><END>
Hello, <NAME_MEMO1>.  I was just puzzling over a problem...<P><END>
You see, a long time ago I wrote a book on Mushrooms.<P><C>
I just received a letter from someone who misunderstood the book and <WB>
accidentally ate a poison one! They lived, thank goodness...<P><END>
In their letter, the person blames me for their own error.<P><C>
What do you think I should do?<P><END>
Explain their error.<END>
Apologize.<END>
You're right. I should help them understand better.<P><END>
Thanks, <NAME_MEMO1>. Now I feel more confident in myself. Now to that letter...<P><END>
You think so...? Maybe I should have written it more clearly, after <WB>
all...!<P><C>
Now I feel horrible. Will you leave me alone now please?<P><END>
