Why can't you act more like a girl?<P><END>
I am who I am!<P><END>
My sister was more girl-like than you are...<P><END>
I'm not your sister! Don't you like me?...<P><END>
Of course I like you!<P><END>
If you really liked me, you'd like me just how I am!<P><END>
And you wouldn't compare me with your sister, either! You wouldn't want me <WB>
to change!<P><END>
I'm sorry... You're right, Ann.<P><C>
I didn't mean to hurt your feelings.<P><C>
I really do like you just the way you are!<P><END>
...I'm sorry too. I didn't mean to get so mad.<P><END>
And...I'll even try to act a little more girl-like for you. Once in a while...<P><END>
That's alright...<P><END>
