Are you really leaving...?<P><END>
Thanks for everything. I do have to go, though. I like it here too much...<P><END>
What are you talking about? What's wrong with liking it here...?<P><END>
Tell everyone thanks for me again.<P><END>
Ann will be so sad. She likes you so much...<P><END>
...Bye now. It's time for me to go.<P><END>
Good luck!<P><END>
Thanks again for everything.<P><END>
Come back any time you want!<P><END>
