You've been drinking our juice and wine again, haven't you!?!<P><END>
I have not!<P><END>
Don't lie to me!<P><C>
What about those bottles under the bed!<P><END>
Err......."<P><END>
I just wanted to research if I could make them better, that's all...<P><END>
Research, huh?<P><C>
Then why do you drink from it every time I go to bed?<P><END>
You don't have to check up on me so much, you know! It's OK to drink a little, isn't it!?<P><END>
You were the one who said you'd stop drinking our sales!<P><C>
You should keep your own promises!<P><C>
After all, Aja left because you can't keep your promises!<P><C>
What if Cliff left for the same reason?<P><C>
I'd never forgive you!<P><END>
............ <P><END>
I never said I wanted you not to drink at all, Duke.<P><C>
I just wanted you to cut back a little, that's all.<P><C>
I'm just because I worry about you, that's all...<P><END>
...OK.<P><END>
Good. I'll forgive you this time.<P><END>
