Hi, <playname>!<P><END>
Yay!! It's <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
Thanks for coming. Stick around for a while.<P><END>
Is the farm keeping you busy?<P><END>
It's not easy running a farm. I admire someone who can do it alone!<P><END>
I could take a lesson from you, yes I could.<P><END>
Elli's working hard, too.<P><C>
It's her day off, but she's studying a medical textbook even so.<P><END>
Quite a sister, she is.<P><END>
It's nothing, really...<P><END>
Oh yeah! I forgot to return that book to the Doctor!<P><C>
Where did I put it...?<P><END>
It was on this shelf... Oh, here it is! Hmm?<P><END>
What's wrong?<P><END>
When I took the book out, a letter came out with it!<P><C>
It's addressed to you, Grandma!<P><END>
What?<P><END>
It's from your Grandpa!<P><END>
Really?!<P><END>
What's it say?<P><END>
Let's see...<P><END>
Dear Ellen, I am writing this on the day our granddaughter Elli is born. I am truly happy, and blessed to have you as my wife. Thank you. When will you read this letter? I'm too embarrassed to give it to you directly, so I'll just hide it here. Please, even if you do come across this, don't tell me you found it. It'll be too embarrassing!<P><END>
I can't believe he wrote this the day I was born!...<P><C>
Why didn't he give this to you then, Grandma?<P><END>
He was very shy and easily embarrassed.<P><C>
I can't believe he even wrote out his feelings like he did!<WB>
He's in heaven now, so I'll treasure this...<P><END>
