Don't you know how to behave, young man?<P><END>
If your purpose was to insult all of us, you've done a good job!<P><END>
Do you know why I'm mad? You should, you know!<P><END>
I don't like you any more!  <P><END>
Young people these days are just no good!<P><END>
How can you do something like that to everybody!?<P><C>
How can you insult us like that?!<P><END>
Now this is quite a mistake you're making. I know everybody makes errors when they're young, but this is really quite inexcusable! Why don't you wise up?<P><END>
You have no excuse! It's an insult to Nature!<P><END>
I don't even know what to say to you...<P><END>
Of course everyone is mad at you! <WB>
It's because of that Golden Lumber!<P><C>
If you respected any of us, you'd take it down now!!<P><END>
Everyone in Mineral Town  is mad at you!<P><C>
If you don't make peace, I'll be forced to arrest you!<P><END>
I like to play jokes on people, too, but this is different! <WB>
How can you be so mean...!?<P><END>
It takes a lot to make me mad, but you've done it this time...!<P><END>
How can you be so thoughtless! And I used to like you, too!<P><END>
The gods will surely punish you if you continue this folly!<P><END>
Are you too dense to figure out what's gotten people so mad!?...<P><END>
Aren't you embarrassed of yourself? You should be!<P><END>
I've even heard about you in the town where I live!<P><C>
You should be ashamed of yourself, you know!<P><END>
You have managed to arouse even my anger. Mend your ways soon!<P><END>
Are you still using Golden Lumber?<P><C>
What a horrid person! It's an insult to everyone, so remove it immediately!<P><END>
