How goes the patrol, Harris?<P><END>
Mineral Town is safe and peaceful, as always.<P><END>
Good to hear... Nothing wrong on the mountain, either.<P><END>
It really should be me patrolling the mountain, not you.<P><C>
Thanks for helping out, Gotz.<P><END>
Don't worry about it. I know more about the mountain than you.<P><C>
Besides, patrolling it was my idea.<P><END>
...........<P><C>
It's been quite a while since your wife and daughter died on the <WB>
mountain.<P><END>
...I think if I can prevent others from meeting the same fate...<P><C>
Those two will rest a little bit more peacefully...<P><END>
...I think so, too.<P><END>
