Sorry to bother you so late, but can I ask you something?<P><END>
Sure.<END>
Not now.<END>
You see...I have a secret crush on Aja, Duke and Manna's daughter who's <WB>
living in the city.<P><END>
I want to write her a letter, but I'm kind of stuck...<P><END>
I thought that you might be a good person to ask advice from.<P><C>
Do you have any idea what I should write to Aja?<P><END>
Tell her how you feel.<END>
Think for yourself.<END>
You're right! I'm thinking too much about it, I guess. Simple is best.<P><END>
Thanks to your advice, I've decided to take a chance and just tell <WB>
Aja how I feel.<P><C>
Thanks a lot!<P><END>
OK...Sorry to bother you...<P><END>
OK...Sorry to bother you.<P><C>
Don't forget to lock you doors at night.<P><END>
