Sorry to bother you so late.<P><END>
I don't look so well? Well, there's a reason.<P><C>
After talking to you, I wrote to Aja and told her everything how I feel <WB>
about her.<P><C>
Her response came today.<P><END>
Aja says that she already has a boyfriend in the city!<P><C>
No luck for me, I guess.<P><END>
No, don't blame yourself. You see, I'm actually very thankful to you.<P><C>
If I hadn't written that letter, I never would have known Aja was in love<WB>
with someone else.<P><C>
But, now I know to give up on her. Thanks again, <NAME_MEMO1>. <WB>
Don't forget to lock you doors at night.<P><END>
