I hear that your latest book is selling like hotcakes, Mary.<P><END>
Yeah, the publisher even wants me to write a sequel!<P><END>
Hmm....<P><END>
Why don't you seem very happy about it, Gray? Aren't you glad for me?<P><END>
It's not like that... It's just that, well...<P><END>
It's not like you to not say what you think, Gray.<P><END>
OK...I'm worried about your health!<P><END>
When you wrote the last book, you stayed up late every night working on it.<P><C>
You were so tired all the time I couldn't help but worry!<P><C>
I didn't want to stop you from doing what you wanted, though.<P><END>
Thanks for caring about me so much, Gray.<P><END>
Of course I do!<P><END>
In that case, I promise not to work so hard writing the next one.<P><END>
I'll try to do what I can to help, too.<P><END>
I'm glad I married you, Gray!<P><END>
Now you're making me embarrassed...!<P><END>
