I wonder if this is the right grass?...<P><END>
Oh! Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
How do you like your married life? Takes some adjusting to, I bet!<P><END>
What was I doing? I'm looking for a grass for my father that he needs <WB>
for his research.<P><END>
That's nice of you.<END>
I see.<END>
I try to help out my dad. Besides, I actually enjoy it!<P><END>
Sorry for interrupting you. I have to get back now.<P><C>
Good luck on the farm!<P><END>
Well, Dad's research really is important, so I like to help out any way I can.<P><END>
