Thanks for coming, Sai.<P><END>
Hi there, Saibara.<P><END>
I was just passing by, so I thought I'd drop in.<P><END>
You're welcome any time, Sai!<P><END>
I wish I could come visit you, but with these legs... I can hardely walk!<P><END>
........<P><END>
I can't even go outside with these legs!<P><END>
I remember when we used to take walks to the mountains, the beach, and lots of <WB>
places together...!<P><C>
Too bad we can't now, all because of these darned legs of mine!<P><END>
Don't say that! I'm sure your legs'll get better, and we can <WB>
take our walks again!<P><END>
Thanks, Sai...<P><END>
It's nothing.... Err...I guess I'll be going, now...<P><END>
Oh, <NAME_MEMO1>! I didn't see you there. What are you doing here?<P><END>
Umm...This is MY house, Saibara!<P><END>
Oh! You're right... Sorry...! Bye now...<P><END>
Saibara can be so strange sometimes!<P><END>
