<NAME_MEMO1>, I hope you can help me out.<P><END>
You see... I got into a boasting match with the Mayor of the next <WB>
town over, and...<P><END>
I have to bring a Diamond to him today. <P><END>
I have to bring a Bracelet to him today. <P><END>
I have to bring a Green Pepper to him today. <P><END>
I have to bring a Golden Egg to him today. <P><END>
I have to bring Black Grass to him today. <P><END>
I have to bring White Grass to him today. <P><END>
I have to bring a Truffle to him today. <P><END>
I have to bring a Moon Stone to him today. <P><END>
I have to bring an AEPFE Apple to him today. <P><END>
I have to bring a Rice Cake to him today. <P><END>
I'm sorry to ask this of you all the sudden, but you're the only person I can <WB>
turn to!<P><C>
I'm counting on you! I don't want to lose face!<P><END>
Can I count on you for this?<P><END>
Sure!<END>
Sorry...<END>
I knew you were the kind of man I could depend on!<P><C>
I'll come by around 7PM to pick it up, OK? I'm very grateful!<P><END>
Really...? I overestimated you, it seems...<P><C>
I'll have to do it myself, I guess...<P><END>
