I'll get today's shipment!<P><END>
You're shipping a lot today! Keep up the good work!<P><END>
What? You have nothing to ship today?<P><END>
Why don't you keep chickens? If you feed them everyday, they'll lay eggs.<P><END>
Why don't you keep cows? If you take good care of them, they'll grow up and<WB>
produce milk.<P><END>
Why don't you keep sheep? If you take good care of them, they'll grow and<WB>
give you wool.<P><END>
There are some ores from the mine that you can sell. Why don't you go dig<WB>
some up?<P><END>
You can got to the lake mine in the winter. I heard there are gems in that one.<WB>
Go dig some up.<P><END>
You can sell some items from the mountains and forests. Go look for them.<P><END>
Why don't you grow some crops? Seeds are at the supermarket.<P><END>
Do you fish? Selling fish will make you money.<P><END>
