<NAME_MEMO1>, where are you going?<P><C>
The competition hasn't started yet!<P><END>
Hmm...What should I make?<P><END>
The judging hasn't even begun yet.<P><END>
Dzui qua xa! Ve lam viec thui...<P><END>
Where are you going? The New Year Festival hasn't even started yet!<P><END>
What are you doing? We haven't eaten the year end noodles yet!<P><END>
There are still races left.<P><END>
Where are you going? It hasn't started yet!<P><END>
Where are you going?<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO1>, The Sheep Festival hasn't ended yet.<P><END>
