About Fishing               <BB>
Once you get a Fishing Rod, <BB>
try some fishing!           <BB>
                            <BB>
How to get the Fishing Rod  <BB>
One of Zack's friends likes <BB>
fishing, so if you go visit <BB>
Zack you might learn        <BB>
something.                  <BB>
                            <BB>
How to Fish                 <BB>
First go to where you think <BB>
there might be some fish,   <BB>
then press the B Button     <BB>
to make your cast. After    <BB>
that, all you can do is wait<BB>
for something to bite.      <BB>
                            <BB>
The rod will shake when a   <BB>
fish takes the bait. If you <BB>
press the B Button quickly  <BB>
enough, you might be able   <BB>
to reel him in.             <BB>
If you aren't fast enough,  <BB>
and let a fish get away,    <BB>
all you can do is wait for  <BB>
the next one. Sometimes you <BB>
just have hard luck, so be  <BB>
patient and make another    <BB>
cast! However, if you fish  <BB>
in the wrong place, you     <BB>
could wait forever without  <BB>
getting a bite, so select   <BB>
your fishing spot carefully.<BB>
                            <BB>
Fishing Locations           <BB>
There are many locations    <BB>
to fish in Mineral Town.    <BB>
                            <BB>
·Sea                        <BB>
You can enjoy fishing from  <BB>
Mineral Beach.              <BB>
                            <BB>
·Downstream                 <BB>
This is the river south of  <BB>
town and your farm.         <BB>
                            <BB>
·Spring                     <BB>
The spring near the mine.   <BB>
                            <BB>
·Upstream                   <BB>
This is the river near the  <BB>
bridge close to the         <BB>
mountain. This spot is very <BB>
narrow, so be careful.      <BB>
                            <BB>
·Lake                       <BB>
This is the large lake      <BB>
near the mountain.          <BB>
                            <BB>
·Other places               <BB>
There might be other places <BB>
to fish, so investigate     <BB>
on your own.                <BB>
