Acquiring a Kitchen         <BB>
You must have a Kitchen to  <BB>
do any cooking.             <BB>
There is no room for a      <BB>
Kitchen in a small house,   <BB>
so you'll have to wait      <BB>
until you expand your       <BB>
house. You will also need   <BB>
a place to hold your        <BB>
Ingredients and Utensils,   <BB>
so you need to buy          <BB>
Shelves and a Refrigerator  <BB>
as well.                    <BB>
After you have all of       <BB>
these, you will be able to  <BB>
buy a Kitchen on the        <BB>
TV Shopping Network.        <BB>
                            <BB>
Next, you will be able to   <BB>
buy Utensils on the TV      <BB>
Shopping Network.           <BB>
The more Utensils you buy,  <BB>
the more kinds of dishes    <BB>
you will be able to cook.   <BB>
