Caring for Animals          <BB>
Animals such as Chickens,   <BB>
Cows, and Sheep are the     <BB>
heart and soul of a farm.   <BB>
They provide you with Eggs, <BB>
Milk, and Wool.             <BB>
If your animals are healthy <BB>
and multiply, your farm will<BB>
be bountiful.               <BB>
                            <BB>
★Chickens                   <BB>
If you take Eggs from your  <BB>
Chickens and put them in the<BB>
Incubator, Chicks will be   <BB>
born in three days. Chicks  <BB>
grow into Chickens in       <BB>
one week.                   <BB>
                            <BB>
★Cows                       <BB>
Adult Cows will supply you  <BB>
with Milk. If you use a     <BB>
Cow Miracle Potion          <BB>
to impregnate a Cow, a      <BB>
Baby Calf will be born in   <BB>
three weeks. If you feed    <BB>
it every day, a Baby Calf   <BB>
will grow into a Calf in    <BB>
two weeks, then into an     <BB>
adult Cow in one            <BB>
more week.                  <BB>
                            <BB>
★Sheep                      <BB>
Sheep produce Wool you      <BB>
can sell. Wool takes one    <BB>
week to grow. If you use a  <BB>
Sheep Miracle Potion to     <BB>
impregnate a Sheep, a Lamb  <BB>
will be born in three       <BB>
weeks. If you feed it       <BB>
every day, a Lamb will      <BB>
grow into an adult Sheep    <BB>
in two weeks.               <BB>
                            <BB>
★Raising Animals            <BB>
It takes lots of work to    <BB>
keep your animals healthy,  <BB>
but this is the core of what<BB>
makes a farm successful.    <BB>
You have to brush them,     <BB>
talk to them, and feed them <BB>
daily. If you forget to feed<BB>
them one day, they will     <BB>
be displeased with you,     <BB>
but brushing them and       <BB>
remembering their daily     <BB>
feeding can help make them  <BB>
happy and healthy again.    <BB>
                            <BB>
Be careful not to hit       <BB>
animals with your farm      <BB>
implements. It will harm    <BB>
them and decrease their     <BB>
affection towards you.      <BB>
                            <BB>
If animals stay unhealthy   <BB>
for an extended period,     <BB>
there is a chance they may  <BB>
get sick. If this happens,  <BB>
use Animal Medicine to      <BB>
heal them. If you don't make<BB>
them better, they'll die.   <BB>
                            <BB>
If you keep your animals as <BB>
healthy as you can, their   <BB>
affection for you will      <BB>
rise and the quality of     <BB>
their Eggs, Milk, and Wool  <BB>
will increase.              <BB>
                            <BB>
★Grazing                    <BB>
You can let your animals    <BB>
graze outside the Barn on   <BB>
your farm. Chickens will    <BB>
start to find worms and     <BB>
other things to eat on      <BB>
the ground. Cows and Sheep  <BB>
will graze on mature Grass. <BB>
Since they like it outside, <BB>
letting animals graze also  <BB>
increases their affection   <BB>
towards you. The fresh air  <BB>
also improves the quality of<BB>
their Eggs, Milk, and Wool, <BB>
so graze them as often as   <BB>
possible when the weather is<BB>
good. However, be careful of<BB>
wild dogs at night          <BB>
