Help from the H. Sprites    <BB>
Have you met the Harvest    <BB>
Sprites who live in the     <BB>
forest?                     <BB>
If you make friends with    <BB>
them, they will help you    <BB>
do work on your farm.       <BB>
                            <BB>
There are 3 jobs they can   <BB>
help you with.              <BB>
"Watering"                  <BB>
They can help water crops.  <BB>
                            <BB>
"Harvest"                   <BB>
They will harvest and ship  <BB>
crops for you.              <BB>
                            <BB>
"Animal Husbandry"          <BB>
They can help take care     <BB>
of your animals by feeding  <BB>
and brushing them, or       <BB>
ship Eggs, Milk, and Wool.  <BB>
                            <BB>
The more the Harvest        <BB>
Sprites help you, the       <BB>
more they like their jobs,  <BB>
and the more efficient      <BB>
they get.                   <BB>
However, if you work them   <BB>
too hard, they will stop    <BB>
liking you. Give them       <BB>
presents to help maintain   <BB>
good relations!             <BB>
