Mini-Game                   <BB>
★"Local Horse Race Hints"   <BB>
                            <BB>
Horse Racing Festival       <BB>
is held the 18th day of     <BB>
Fall and Spring in Rose     <BB>
Square.                     <BB>
The Mayor will come let you <BB>
know the day before, so if  <BB>
you have a Horse, you should<BB>
enter the race. But, you    <BB>
can't enter with a pony.    <BB>
Use the A Button to whip    <BB>
your Horse to go faster.    <BB>
If you use it too much,     <BB>
though, the Horse will tire <BB>
quickly, so you have to     <BB>
pace it well. Also, when    <BB>
betting on the race, don't  <BB>
always go for the sure      <BB>
winner. Sometimes it's good <BB>
to take a chance!           <BB>
If you take good care of    <BB>
your Horse and practice     <BB>
riding it fast often, you'll<BB>
do better in races.         <BB>
Good luck!                  <BB>
                            <BB>
----------------------------<BB>
★ Chicken Festival Hints    <BB>
                            <BB>
The Chicken Festival        <BB>
is held on the 7th day of   <BB>
every Summer in Rose Square.<BB>
Rick will come around the   <BB>
day before to let you know, <BB>
so if you have a Chicken,   <BB>
you can enter the Festival. <BB>
However, sick Chickens and  <BB>
Chicks are not eligible.    <BB>
To win, press the A Button  <BB>
to help your Chicken        <BB>
intimidate the opposing     <BB>
Chicken to drive it out of  <BB>
the ring.                   <BB>
The trick is to keep your   <BB>
Chicken's affection up.     <BB>
If the Chicken's affection  <BB>
is low, it won't do well.   <BB>
Increase affection by       <BB>
treating your Chicken well  <BB>
and building up a good      <BB>
relationship with it.       <BB>
Enter your Chicken with     <BB>
the highest affection into  <BB>
the competition. Good luck! <BB>
