Introducing Vesta           <BB>
Vesta runs the farm along   <BB>
the banks of Forget-me-not  <BB>
Valley's river.             <BB>
<261>                       <BB>
She ships her produce to    <BB>
town, but will also give    <BB>
away Seeds to those who     <BB>
need them.                  <BB>
<262>                       <BB>
                            <BB>
She lost her husband long   <BB>
ago, so lives with her      <BB>
brother Marlin and her      <BB>
distant relative Celia.     <BB>
