Introducing Galen           <BB>
He moved to Forget-me-not   <BB>
Valley to spend his         <BB>
retirement with his wife    <BB>
Nina.                       <BB>
He can be quite stubborn    <BB>
but is usually happy.       <BB>
<101>                       <BB>
                            <BB>
When Nina died, he built a  <BB>
cottage near her grave      <BB>
on a hill, where he spends  <BB>
all day watching the ocean. <BB>
