Introducing Romana          <BB>
She used to be a wealthy    <BB>
woman in town, but she took <BB>
her butler Sebastian and her<BB>
granddaughter Lumina to     <BB>
Forget-me-not Valley so she <BB>
could have a quiet          <BB>
retirement.                 <BB>
<011>                       <BB>
                            <BB>
She still likes to have fun,<BB>
though, and it's her habit  <BB>
to hide things for          <BB>
townspeople to find them.   <BB>
<012>                       <BB>
                            <BB>
She doesn't talk much about <BB>
her past, but many years ago<BB>
the cruise ship she was on  <BB>
with her husband sank,      <BB>
leaving her a widow.        <BB>
