Xin chao! Ten ban la <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><C>
Toi la Chef. Budum! Moi vao. Budum!<P><END>
Tiec tra se dien ra vao mua Xuan, budum.<P><END>
Ban co mang theo giay moi khong? Moi nguoi! Chuan bi bo am tra!...<P><END>
Xin loi, nhung chua du moi nguoi o day, budum, nen chung ta khong the to chuc tiec tra ngay bay gio.<P><END>
Bay gio khong phai thoi diem de to chuc tiec tra, budum. Hay den dung gio!<P><END>
Chung ta khong the to chuc tiec tra o day, budum!<P><END>
Day la qua sinh nhat, budum! Cam on! <P><END>
Yipee!! No that tuyet voi! Budum! Cam on ban!<P><END>
Cam on! No that tuyet! Budum!<P><END>
Cam on! Vudum...<P><END>
Toi khong thich no.  Budum...<P><END>
.......!! Day la mon qua te nhat, budum...<P><END>
Awww...No de thuong qua, budum!<P><END>
T-Tai sao...hinh nhu no muon an song toi, budum...?<P><END>
Cam on rat nhieu! No thuc su danh cho toi, budum?<P><END>
Cam on ban! Toi rat vui!<END>
No la mot chiec long tuyet voi, nhung no khong the lam toi no, budum.<P><END>
Toi nghe co tin don rang toi co ban be o Forget-me-not Valley, budum?<P><END>
Mua Xuan la mua cua tiec tra. Moi nguoi deu thich tiec tra, budum!<P><END>
Mua Xuan la mua cua tiec tra. Chung toi se moi nhung nguoi ban than thiet.<P><END>
Mua Xuan la mua cua tiec Tra. Ban co thich tra khong?<P><END>
Mua Xuan la mua cua tiec tra. Neu ban den, chung toi se to chuc moi ngay, budum!<P><END>
Toi thich tiec tra vi no la loai do uong tuyet voi, budum.<P><END>
Chef la nguoi chieu dai tiec tra, budum.<P><END>
Chung toi chi moi nhung nguoi ban that su den du tiec!<P><END>
I wish everyday is the Spring so that we can have a tea party everyday.<P><END>
I'm getting hungry, budum...<P><END>
Did you bring anything for me to eat, budum?<P><END>
Ah, <NAME_MEMO1>. What will you give me today, budum?<P><END>
Whenever I get hungry, you seem to come along, budum.<P><END>
I just love to eat!...<P><END>
If I don't eat, I don't have any energy, budum...<P><END>
You know what I like to eat, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
If it were for you, <NAME_MEMO1>, I'd be willing to work even if I got hungry!<P><END>
Ban can giup gi khong?<P><END>
Can you help me?<END>
Let's play.<END>
Nothing in particular.<END>
I'll get started tomorrow, budum.<P><END>
I'll help you if we become better friends, budum.<P><END>
What should I do?<P><END>
Watering<END>
Harvest<END>
Animals<END>
Exit<END>
How long do you want me to water for, budum?<P><END>
1 day<END>
3 days<END>
1 week<END>
Got it. I'll water for 1 day, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll water for 3 days, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll water for 1 week, budum.<P><END>
How many days do you want me to harvest for, budum?<P><END>
Got it. I'll harvest for 1 day, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll harvest for 3 days, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll harvest for 1 week, budum.<P><END>
How long do you want me to look after the animals for, budum?<P><END>
Got it. I'll look after the animals for 1 day, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll look after the animals for 3 days, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll look after the animals for 1 week, budum.<P><END>
Really, budum? Is that so...?<P><END>
We already played today! Let's play tomorrow, budum.<P><END>
I'll play if we become better friends, budum.<P><END>
How should we play?<P><END>
Let's play the watering game, budum!<P><END>
I think I've gotten better than before, budum!<P><END>
I hope I don't make too many mistakes...<P><END>
Let's play the harvest game, budum!<P><END>
Let's play the animal husbandry game, budum!<P><END>
What? You don't want to play, budum? That's too bad...<P><END>
No?<P><END>
We're already done working for the day!<P><END>
I haven't gotten very good at it yet, budum...<P><END>
I think I'm getting the hang of it, budum...!<P><END>
Harvesting is fun, budum! Let's do more!<P><END>
Now I'm a master harvester! Just leave it to me, budum!<P><END>
Watering is fun, budum! Let's do more!<P><END>
Gio toi tuoi cay rat gioi! Hay de no cho toi, budum!<P><END>
Taking care of animals is fun, budum! Let's do more!<P><END>
Now I'm great at taking care of the animals! Just leave it to me, budum!<P><END>
Let's do more tomorrow!<END>
Your job is done for now.<END>
I'll do my best, budum.<P><END>
OK. Tomorrow I'll rest, budum.<P><END>
