Oh, I'd forgotten! Thanks for the great birthday present!<P><END>
What a fantastic gift! How did you know I love these so much? Thanks!<P><END>
This is for me? Gee, thanks...I love these!<P><END>
Wow, thanks... I'll remember this!<P><END>
Err...Thanks...<P><END>
Are you trying to goad me into losing my temper, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
I guess you're used to bugs, if you work on a farm!<P><END>
Yikes! Get it away from me!<P><END>
Now this is a great one...! Thanks! I think I'll give it to Harris' wife when<WB>
he gets married!<P><END>
Well this is very fancy!<P><C>
Oh...You mean it's for me? I can't exactly use it, but I'll give it to <WB>
Harris' wife when he gets<WB>
married.<P><END>
I bet the animals get scared when you put this on!<P><C>
Oh, it's for me? Thanks!<P><END>
Congratulations! Who's the lucky girl, if I may ask?<P><END>
Have you heard of the Forget-me-not Valley?<P><C>
I hear there's someone there named <MF>, who is very popular.<P><C>
I'd like to meet him...<P><END>
A long time ago, someone named Kano used to stay at my house.<P><C>
He used to love taking pictures of Mineral Town.<P><C>
One day, though, he just left a letter and vanished.<P><C>
I wonder where he is now?<P><END>
There's nothing more pleasing to a mayor than a peaceful village!<P><END>
You should at least rest on the weekends, <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
I bet that's not going to happen though, is it?<P><END>
Hmmm...Looks like it's not going to stop.<P><C>
And I was going to go to the Square, too!<P><END>
Ellen and I always eat Apple Pie together on the weekends.<P><C>
The Apple Pie at the Inn is the best!<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. I'm off to go shopping!<P><END>
A! La cau day a,  <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><C>
Cau thay cuoc song moi nhu the nao?   <P><END>
Ta nghi cau phai xay dung lai nong trai...<P><C>
Nong trai do da hoan toan bi bo hoang... <P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>! Have you gotten the hang of farming, yet?<P><END>
Myself...I know more about running towns than farms!<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>! I hear you've been doing mighty well at the farm!<P><END>
People like me depend on people like you to grow our food, <WB>
so you have my gratitude!<P><END>
Hey there, <NAME_MEMO1>. Did you come here for a rest, too?<P><END>
I bet the animals are happy on days like today, eh?<P><END>
Hello, <NAME_MEMO1>. Have you come to like our town yet?<P><END>
Just come to me if you ever get into any trouble. I give great advice.<P><END>
Do you think this rain will continue...?<P><END>
I was going to the Square, so I wish it were sunny...<P><C>
Is there something new up on the bulletin board? I forget.<P><END>
Too bad about this rain...<P><C>
And it's my day off, too!<P><END>
Harris always comes by the Inn at this hour, so I like to wait for him here on <WB>
rainy days.<P><C>
Just to make sure everything is OK, you understand.<P><END>
