Do you want an explanation?<END>
Yes<END>
Yes<END>
No<END>
No<END>
<C>The cursor on the gauge to the left will start to move when the game starts.<WB>
Press the A Button to stop the cursor with the correct timing.<P><END>
<C>The green zone shows how far your dog can catch the frisbee.<P><END>
<C>The red zone shows where the frisbee can't be caught.<WB>
Be sure to catch the frisbee inside the green zone.<P><END>
<C>The more you practice, the greater your dog's range becomes<WB>
However, if you practice too much at once, your dog will get bored.<WB>
If this happens he won't play any more. The higher your dog's affection is<WB>
toward you, the more he will practice.<P><END>
<C>In the Frisbee Tournament, you get two tries. The better throw is used.<P><END>
Explain again?<END>
<C>Now throw again.<P><END>
<C>The Tournament is over.<P><END>
Play again?<END>
<C>Your dog doesn't seem to want to play anymore.<P><END>
<C>You found a <NAME_MEMO1><P><END>
<C>You didn't find anything.<P><END>
