The theme for this year is Juice! I can't wait to taste everybody's efforts!<P><END>
The theme for this year is Desserts! Make some irresistible Desserts!<P><END>
The theme for this year is Bread! Make some great fresh Bread!<P><END>
The theme for this year is Noodles! Make some Noodles no one can resist!<P><END>
The theme for this year is Rice. Go make some creative Rice dishes for us!<P><END>
