Tomorrow is the Fall Horse Racing in the Square.<P><C>
If you have a Horse that can enter, you should give it a try.<P><END>
Tomorrow is the Fall Horse Racing in the Square.<P><C>
If you have a good Horse, you should try entering.<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. Tomorrow is the Horse Races in the Square.<P><C>
You thinking of entering?<P><END>
Yes.<END>
No.<END>
In that case, I'll take <NAME_MEMO5> with me now. Be there by 10AM tomorrow!<P><END>
That's too bad. You should still come and bet on the races, though. It's fun!<P><END>
