I'm looking forward to hearing you play Ocarina.<P><C>
Are you ready yet?<P><END>
I'm ready.<END>
Wait a minute.<END>
OK... Everyone, we're on!<P><END>
What's wrong? When you do get ready, just let me know.<P><END>
You can't play the Ocarina if you're holding anything. Please put that down first.<P><END>
You aren't performing with us this time, right?<P><C>
Just sit back and enjoy the music!<P><END>
