Well, should we start the New Year Festival now?<P><END>
...But, you can't participate while your hands are full!<P><END>
Start<END>
Wait a minute<END>
Alright, let's get started.  <P><END>
Well, let me know when you're ready. <P><END>
Shall we get started on the new year celebration?<P><END>
...But, you can't eat while your hands are full, can you?<P><END>
Start.<END>
Hold on a second.<END>
Let's eat, then!  <P><END>
Just let me know when you're ready to eat. <P><END>
Long table<P><END>
