Shuffle...shuffle...<P><END>
I can't believe his Rucksack is so full. This won't even fit!<P><END>
Now what'll I do...? Why does he wear his Rucksack even when he's<P><C>
sleeping? Great! It fit!<P><END>
Hmm...shuffle...shuffle....<P><END>
I was gonna give it to you if you had a space in your rucksack, but...<WB>
Oh well, I guess I'll eat it.<P><END>
I hope he wakes up soon! I can't wait to see the look on his face!<P><END>
Shuffle...shuffle....<P><END>
Shoot! I never thought of what to do if his Rucksack was full...!<P><END>
...?? Thank goodness he didn't wake up!<P><END>
Darn it! His Rucksack is already full!<P><C>
I can't take anything out either...Oh, I give up!!<P><END>
...<NAME_MEMO2>'s asleep. I can't wait to see the look on his face!<P><END>
Darn it! His Rucksack is full! I hope I remember to give it to him later.<P><END>
I wonder if <NAME_MEMO2> even knows that today is the Winter Thanksgiving<WB>
Festival?<P><C>
I'll just put this in his Rucksack!...<P><END>
What...? He's asleep?<P><END>
How dare his Rucksack be full, even though I went to all this effort...!<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO1>, I brought something nice for you! Wake up!<P><C>
He's sleeping like a log! I know...I'll put it in his Rucksackl!<P><END>
