The Sheep Festival is tomorrow at Rose Square.<P><C>
Any adult Sheep that isn't pregnant, sick, or shorn can compete.<P><C>
I hope to see an entry from <NAME_MEMO3> next year. <WB>
Hope to see you tomorrow!<P><END>
The Sheep Festival is tomorrow at Rose Square.<P><C>
Any adult Sheep that isn't pregnant, sick, or shorn can compete.<P><C>
I hope to see a Sheep from <NAME_MEMO3> next year. <WB>
It's fun; I hope you come!<P><END>
The Sheep Festival is tomorrow at Rose Square.<P><C>
Do you want to enter a Sheep from <NAME_MEMO3>?<P><END>
Sure!<END>
Not this year.<END>
Will you select which Sheep? Remember, it has to be adult, and can't be sick, <WB>
pregnant, or shorn.<P><END>
Really? And I thought your Sheep had a good chance, too...<P><END>
The Sheep Festival is tomorrow at Rose Square.<P><C>
Any adult Sheep that isn't pregnant, sick, or shorn can compete.<P><C>
You don't have any eligible Sheep, but I hope you can come watch anyway!<P><END>
I'll bring this one with me now, then. Don't forget to come tomorrow.<P><END>
