Today is the Starry Night Festival. It took a lot of effort to make all this<WB>
food, so eat up!<P><END>
Today is the Starry Night Festival. I made some delicious food, so <WB>
let's eat together!<P><END>
Look at this feast! Let's start our Starry Night Festival.<P><END>
Today my mom made some cake for the Starry Night Festival. <WB>
Tell me what you think of everything!<P><END>
Why do you look so surprised? Even I can make something good for the <WB>
Starry Night Festival.<P><C>
Let's eat!<P><END>
I made a delicious feast for the Starry Night Festival.<P><C>
Let's eat it together, alright?<P><END>
It took all day to make this feast for the Starry Night Festival.<P><C>
Let's us 3 eat up!<P><END>
It took all day to make this dinner for the Starry Night Festival.<P><C>
Let's us 3 eat up!<P><END>
It took all day to make this feast for the Starry Night Festival.<P><C>
Let's us 3 enjoy it!<P><END>
Goo-goo!<P><END>
Let's go to the mountaintop! We shouldn't spend the whole Starry Night <WB>
Festival indoors!<P><END>
They say this is when the stars are the prettiest. Let's go look, OK?<P><END>
You're already tired? Can't you at least climb the mountain?<P><END>
The stars should be out by now. Let's go to the mountaintop.<P><END>
This is perfect star-viewing weather, isn't it?<P><C>
Let's go look later.<P><END>
Want to go to the mountaintop to look at the best stars of the year <WB>
with me?<P><END>
I never get tired of looking at the stars from here.<P><C>
They're so beautiful...<P><END>
No matter how many times I see them, they change.<P><C>
People don't think so, but the mountain and stars are alive too, you know!<P><END>
When I see a whole sky full of stars like this, it fills me with wonder.<P><END>
I wonder if there is someone out there looking at our star and thinking<WB>
the same thing...?<P><END>
Look! A falling star..!!<WB>
Did you see it?<P><END>
Oh darn, I forgot to make a wish!<P><END>
These stars we're looking at now may not even exist any more...<P><END>
But even though they may be gone, their light still reaches us...<P><END>
Look at all the stars...<WB>
When my parents died, my grandmother could still walk, so she took me <WB>
up here one night...<P><END>
She told me I could come up here whenever I wanted and be with my parents again.<P><END>
It seems like I'm always staring down at the ground.<P><C>
It feels good to stare up at the sky once in a while!<P><END>
I'd love to stay up here with you forever, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><C>
But, the job of a Harvest Goddess never ends.<P><C>
I need a vacation!<P><END>
That was fun! I know I'll sleep well tonight...<P><END>
