You don't have enough money for the Medicine. I'm terribly sorry.<P><END>
Sure you don't need anything else?<P><END>
Sure you don't need anything? It looks like you should get more rest...<P><END>
Do you need anything else?<P><END>
Since you can't hold anything else, I'll have this delivered for you.<P><END>
Looks like you can't hold all this. I'll have the rest delivered for you.<P><END>
Here you go. Take care, now.<P><END>
