Thanks any time! Ach! You can't fit anything more in your Rucksack!<P><C>
I'll send it along, though. No worries, no worries!<P><END>
Thanks any time! Ach! You can't fit anything more in your Rucksack!<P><C>
I'll send it along, though. No worries, no worries!<P><END>
Thanks any time! Ach! Some won't fit into your Rucksack!<P><C>
I'll send it along, though. No worries, no worries!<P><END>
Thanks any time! Ach! Some won't fit into your Rucksack!<P><C>
I'll send it along, though. No worries, no worries!<P><END>
Thanks very much now! Do business any time!<P><END>
Thanks very much now! Do business any time!<P><END>
Your Gold in insufficient! Do these eyes look blind to you!?...<P><END>
Want to buy anything else? Extra cheap for you...<P><END>
...Are you playing games with me?<P><END>
Sure you don't want to buy anything else?<P><END>
