You must give your Chickens Chicken Feed everyday.<P><C>
Take the Feed from the Feed Bin and put it in the Feed Boxes.<P><END>
Put one bushel of Feed in the Feed Box for every Chicken you have.<P><C>
If you don't give them enough, your Chickens will become unhappy.<P><END>
To raise healthy animals, it's necessary to spend lots of time with them.<P><END>
Press the A Button close to your Chickens to lift them up.<P><END>
Press the A Button again to set the Chicken back down. This is how you increase <WB>
affection of your Chickens.<P><END>
Next, ship the Eggs laid by your Chickens.<P><END>
Press the A Button next to an Egg to pick it up.<P><END>
Bring the Egg to the Shipment Box and press the A Button again to ship it.<P><END>
If your Chickens become sick, you can heal them with Animal Medicine.<P><C>
This may be purchased at the Poultry Farm or Yodel Farm.<P><END>
You can heal sick Chickens by using Animal Medicine next to them.<P><END>
The Chicken is healed!<P><END>
Place the Egg in the Incubator.<P><END>
After picking an Egg up, face the Incubator and press the A Button.<P><END>
After 3 days...<P><END>
A baby Chick is born!<P><END>
Finally, let your Chickens out to graze.<P><END>
Lift a Chicken up and bring it outside the Chicken Coop.<P><END>
Put the Chicken down outside.<P><END>
Several hours after being let out to graze, your Chickens will find worms and<WB>
other food on their own.<P><C>
Pick up the Chickens and bring them back into the Chicken Coop.<P><END>
