Song o nong trai<SB>
                  ADVANCED 1<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"What will you teach me   <SB>
 about today?"            <SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 the wandering salesman,   <SB>
 Won. Lately he's staying  <SB>
 at Zack's house in Mineral<SB>
 Beach, where he's selling <SB>
 his wares.                <SB>
 You can buy Seeds, Dog    <SB>
 Training Tools, or Jewels <SB>
 of Truth from him.        <SB>
 Some of the Seeds he has  <SB>
 they don't carry at the   <SB>
 Supermarket.              <SB>
 He also has Balls and     <SB>
 Frisbees for Dogs. You    <SB>
 can find books on those at<SB>
 the Library, I think.     <SB>
 I'm not sure what Jewels  <SB>
 of Truth are for, but I   <SB>
 think you can get some-   <SB>
 thing when you collect    <SB>
 9..."                    <SB>
"I wonder what it is?..."<P><END>
Song o nong trai<SB>
                  ADVANCED 2<SB>
                           <SB>
"Chi hai oi!"            <SB>
"Cai gi?"                <SB>
"Hay day em ve Control!" <SB>
"Duoc! Truoc tien chi se<SB>
day em cach di chuyen tren<SB>
Map Screen.<SB>
                   <SB>
 ☆Control Pad:            <SB>
 ·Di hoac Chay           <SB>
"Tu 'hoac' nghia la gi a?"<SB>
"Em co the chinh lai nut  <SB>
Control Pad bang cach dung <SB>
bang Menu Movement Setting <SB>
trong cuon nhat ki Dairy.  <SB>
.Chon lua 1 la Di.         <SB>
.Chon lua 2 la Chay."     <SB>
"Vay lam the nao de thay doi<SB>
cac hanh dong da chon?"  <SB>
"Hay nhan R Button de:    <SB>
.Chay voi chon lua 1.      <SB>
.Di voi chon lua 2."      <SB>
"Hieu roi! Vay em se dung <SB>
Control Pad de Di va nut   <SB>
R Button de Chay,<SB>
hoac chinh nguoc lai voi<SB>
Menu Movement Setting."<SB>
"Dung roi!"   <P><END>
Song o nong trai<SB>
                  ADVANCED 3<SB>
                           <SB>
"Chi hai oi!"            <SB>
"Gi nua?"                <SB>
"Hay day them cho em ve   <SB>
Control di nao!"          <SB>
"Duoc roi! Hom nay chi se <SB>
day them cach di chuyen tren<SB>
Map Screen."              <SB>
                           <SB>
 ☆A Button:               <SB>
 ·Noi chuyen voi moi nguoi<SB>
 ·Kiem tra moi thu        <SB>
 ·Nhat Item len           <SB>
 ·Nem Item di             <SB>
                           <SB>
Ngoai ra, neu em noi chuyen<SB>
voi ai do khi dang cam Item<SB>
thi em se tang Item dang cam<SB>
cho nguoi em noi chuyen," <SB>
"Vay tuc la tang qua?"   <SB>
"Phai, nhung em khong the <SB>
tang qua cho vat nuoi, hoac<SB>
tang nhung thu quan trong  <SB>
nhu la Basket."           <SB>
"Em hieu..."             <P><END>
Song o nong trai<SB>
                  ADVANCED 4<SB>
                           <SB>
"Chi hai oi!"            <SB>
"Gi nua?"                <SB>
"Day cho em biet them ve  <SB>
 Control di nao!"         <SB>
"Thoi duoc, mot so thong tin<SB>
ve nut A Button.         <SB>
Em co the kiem tra moi thu <SB>
nhu bien bao, lich tuong, <SB>
hay ke sach...<SB>
De xem ben trong hoac<SB>
ben tren do co gi. <SB>
Di nhien thong thuong em se<SB>
chang tim thay gi ca.      <SB>
Va di nhien em khong the   <SB>
cam them thu gi khi em     <SB>
dang cam thu gi do."      <SB>
"That sao?"             <SB>
"Di nhien roi.<SB>
Vi the truoc khi kiem tra<SB>
thu gi do, hay chac chan la<SB>
tay em khong co cam bat ki<SB>
thu gi ca!"     <SB>
"Vang! Em ro roi!"       <SB>
"Con nua, em cung khong the<SB>
nhat thu gi do qua nang... <SB>
Vi du nhu la Large Stone."<P><END>
Song o nong trai<SB>
                 ADVANCED 5<SB>
              <SB>
"Chi hai oi!"<SB>
"Gi vay?"<SB>
"Hay day them cho em<SB>
ve Control!"<SB>
"Duoc roi! Chi se day<SB>
tiep ve di chuyen tren<SB>
Map Screen.<SB>
<SB>
Thuc ra nhung dieu ma chi <SB>
day em ngay hom qua ve nut<SB>
A Button van chua thuc su<SB>
day du.<SB>
Neu giu nut A Button<SB>
khi kiem tra thi se<SB>
khong tac dung,<SB>
em phai buong A Button ra."<SB>
"Nghia la sao a?"<SB>
"Vi du, neu em dung truoc<SB>
mot bien bao va giu<SB>
A Button, em se khong thay<SB>
bat ki cai gi cho den khi<SB>
em tha nut A Button ra."<SB>
"Hieu roi!<SB>
Vay sao hom qua chi khong<SB>
noi ro cho em biet?"<SB>
"Boi vi chi khong muon<SB>
lam cho em thay kho hieu."<SB>
"Hum..."<SB>
"Va neu em giu nut A Button<SB>
roi nhan them nut khac thi<SB>
no se co tac dung khac.<SB>
Nhung chi se noi ro hon<SB>
vao ngay mai.<SB>
Bay gio da den<SB>
gio di ngu roi day."  <P><END>
Song o nong trai<SB>
                 ADVANCED 6<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"I was talking about other<SB>
 controls while holding down<SB>
 the A Button, right?<SB>
<SB>
 Hold down the A Button,<SB>
 then press the B Button to<SB>
 switch to the Tools and<SB>
 Items Screen, or press the<SB>
 L Button to switch Items<SB>
 you're holding."<SB>
"What do you mean?"<SB>
"After holding down the A<SB>
 Button and pressing the L<SB>
 Button, use the Control<SB>
 Pad or the L Button to<SB>
 switch what you're holding<SB>
 with something in your<SB>
 Rucksack.<SB>
 Of course, you can't put<SB>
 things like animals in<SB>
 your Rucksack!"<SB>
"So you can switch Items<SB>
 you're holding on the Map<SB>
 Screen. That's useful.<SB>
 Do you have to hold down<SB>
 the A Button the whole<SB>
 time?"As long as you hold down<SB>
 either the A Button or the<SB>
 L Button, you'll be able<SB>
 to keep switching Items."<SB>
"I see."<P><END>
Song o nong trai<SB>
                 ADVANCED 7<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"I was talking about other<SB>
 controls while holding down<SB>
 the A Button, right? "<SB>
<SB>
 If you press the R Button<SB>
 while holding down the A<SB>
 Button, it will cancel the<SB>
 A Button, and you will<SB>
 return to walking or<SB>
 running."<SB>
"You mean Option 1 or 2,<SB>
 which you choose in the<SB>
 Movement Settings in the<SB>
 Diary in the Menu Window,<SB>
 right?"<SB>
"Yeah, where you can set<SB>
 which controls to use for<SB>
 walking and which for<SB>
 running.<SB>
 I'll teach you about some-<SB>
 thing else tomorrow."<SB>
"OK. Bye now."<P><END>
Song o nong trai<SB>
                  ADVANCED 8<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more about      <SB>
 controls!"               <SB>
"OK, here's more about    <SB>
 moving around on the Map  <SB>
 Screen.                   <SB>
                           <SB>
 ☆B Button:               <SB>
 ·Use equipped Item       <SB>
 ·Put away what you're    <SB>
    holding                <SB>
 Use equipped Items is easy<SB>
 enough. You can't use     <SB>
 anything if you're not    <SB>
 holding it!"             <SB>
"Other than things like   <SB>
 Seeds, Animal Medicine,   <SB>
 and Cow and Sheep Miracle <SB>
 Potion, you can use a Tool<SB>
 as many times as you like,<SB>
 right?"                  <SB>
"That's true, but you do  <SB>
 use up your Stamina."    <SB>
"What does that mean?"   <SB>
"I'll explain that        <SB>
 tomorrow!"               <SB>
"OK..."                  <P><END>
Song o nong trai<SB>
                  ADVANCED 9<SB>
                           <SB>
"Chi hai oi!"            <SB>
"Gi vay?"                <SB>
"Hay day tiep cho em ve   <SB>
bai hoc hom qua."         <SB>
"Chi dang giai thich rang <SB>
su dung Tool se lam giam   <SB>
Stamina phai khong?<SB>
Chi nghi em nen hoc<SB>
ve he thong dieu khien<SB>
don gian truoc."    <SB>
"Vang...Thoi duoc..."    <SB>
"Bay gio hay nho lai viec <SB>
cat Item vao Rucksack bang <SB>
B Button tren Map Screen.  <SB>
Nhung do khong phai Tool   <SB>
em dang trang bi ma la nhung<SB>
thu em cam tren tay.       <SB>
Di nhien khi Rucksack day, <SB>
em khong the cat them bat ki<SB>
thu gi vao trong Rucksack. <SB>
Tuy nhien em co the mua<SB>
Larger Rucksack tai<SB>
Supermarket."<SB>
"Em hieu..."          <P><END>
Song o nong trai<SB>
                 ADVANCED 10<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more about      <SB>
 controls!"               <SB>
"OK, here's more about    <SB>
 moving around on the Map  <SB>
 Screen.                   <SB>
                           <SB>
 Just as with the A Button,<SB>
 it's not pushing the B    <SB>
 Button that activates it, <SB>
 but releasing it.         <SB>
 You can do different things<SB>
 by pushing other buttons  <SB>
 while holding down the B  <SB>
 Button. For example, push <SB>
 the A Button while holding<SB>
 down the B Button to move <SB>
 to the Tools and Items    <SB>
 Screen..."               <SB>
"Didn't you mention that  <SB>
 for the A Button, too?"  <SB>
"Yes, good memory. You can<SB>
 view the inside of your   <SB>
 Rucksack by pushing both  <SB>
 the A and B Buttons in    <SB>
 whichever order you like."<SB>
"I see!"                 <SB>
"That's it for today."   <P><END>
Song o nong trai<SB>
                 ADVANCED 11<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"I was talking about other<SB>
 controls while holding down<SB>
 the B Button, right?      <SB>
                           <SB>
 Press the L Button while  <SB>
 holding down the B Button <SB>
 to switch Tools equipped."<SB>
"Is that like switching   <SB>
 Items with the A Button?"<SB>
"Exactly! Use the Control <SB>
 Pad or the L Button to    <SB>
 decide which Tool in your <SB>
 Rucksack you want to switch<SB>
 the current one with.     <SB>
 As long as you hold down  <SB>
 either the B Button or the<SB>
 L Button, you'll be able  <SB>
 to keep switching Tools."<SB>
"That's the same as with  <SB>
 Items, too!"             <P><END>
Song o nong trai<SB>
                 ADVANCED 12<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"I was talking about other<SB>
 controls while holding down<SB>
 the B Button, right? "   <SB>
                           <SB>
 You can switch Tools by   <SB>
 holding down the B Button <SB>
 and pressing the L Button,<SB>
 but not if you're holding <SB>
 something."              <SB>
"Why not?"               <SB>
"Because if it's food,    <SB>
 you have to eat it!"     <SB>
"I see!"                 <SB>
"If you press the R Button<SB>
 while holding down the B  <SB>
 Button, it will cancel the<SB>
 B Button, and you will    <SB>
 return to walking or      <SB>
 running."                <SB>
"That's the same as for   <SB>
 the A Button, right?"    <SB>
"Right. Option 1 or 2,    <SB>
 which you choose in the   <SB>
 Movement Settings in the  <SB>
 Diary in the Menu Window. <SB>
 That's it for the B Button,<SB>
 so I'll teach you about   <SB>
 something else tomorrow."<SB>
"OK. Bye bye."           <P><END>
Song o nong trai<SB>
                 ADVANCED 13<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more about      <SB>
 controls!"               <SB>
"OK, here's more about    <SB>
 moving around on the Map  <SB>
 Screen.                   <SB>
                           <SB>
 ☆L Button:               <SB>
 ·Whistle                 <SB>
                           <SB>
 First, you only Whistle   <SB>
 when you release the L    <SB>
 Button, not when you press<SB>
 it. Also, if you just use <SB>
 the L  Button, you'll call<SB>
 both your Dog and Horse   <SB>
 to you. If you press the  <SB>
 Control Pad Up or Left at <SB>
 the same time, though, you<SB>
 will only call your Dog.  <SB>
 If you press the Control  <SB>
 Pad Down or Right at the  <SB>
 same time, you will       <SB>
 only call your Horse."   <SB>
"I see..."               <P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more  <SB>
 about the L Button."     <SB>
"It seemed difficult<SB>
 just to whistle..."<SB>
"Remember, you can just use<SB>
 the L Button, but that will<SB>
 call both your Dog and    <SB>
 Horse."                  <SB>
"I guess you're right."  <SB>
"If you hold down the L   <SB>
 Button and press the B    <SB>
 Button, you can change    <SB>
 Tools equipped. If you    <SB>
 press the A Button instead,<SB>
 you can change Items..." <SB>
"You taught me that before,<SB>
 right?"                  <SB>
"Right. Finally, hold down<SB>
 the L Button and press    <SB>
 START to view the Town    <SB>
 Map, or SELECT to view the<SB>
 Farm Map."               <SB>
"What are those?"        <SB>
"I'll leave that for      <SB>
 tomorrow!"               <P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more  <SB>
about Map Screen controls."<SB>
                           <SB>
 ☆START                   <SB>
 ·Open the Menu Window    <SB>
                           <SB>
 Press START to open the   <SB>
 Menu Window at the bottom <SB>
 of the screen. The icons  <SB>
 displayed are (from the   <SB>
 left):                    <SB>
 ·Diary                   <SB>
 ·Rucksack                <SB>
 ·Town Map                <SB>
 ·Farm Map                <SB>
 ·Tai san                 <SB>
 ·Ho so                   <SB>
 ·Huong dan               <SB>
 I'll start from the first <SB>
 one, Diary. We're out of  <SB>
 time now, though..."     <SB>
"OK."                    <P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more about      <SB>
 controls!"               <SB>
"Today's lesson will be   <SB>
 on the Menu Window.       <SB>
 First, I'll explain about <SB>
 the Diary.                <SB>
 ...But first, I ought to  <SB>
 explain  the Menu         <SB>
 Window Controls.          <SB>
 All you do is move the    <SB>
 cursor Left and Right with<SB>
 the Control Pad, switch   <SB>
 to the selected screen with<SB>
 the A Button, or close the<SB>
 Menu Window with the B    <SB>
 Button or START."        <SB>
"You don't use the other  <SB>
buttons?"                 <SB>
"Nope! I'll explain about <SB>
 your diary tomorrow."    <SB>
"If you say so."         <P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"I was telling you about  <SB>
 the Diary in the Menu     <SB>
 Window, right?            <SB>
                           <SB>
 The main purpose of the   <SB>
 Diary is to save and load <SB>
 games."                  <SB>
"What else?"            <SB>
"You can also change these:<SB>
 ·Movement Settings       <SB>
 ·Clock Display           <SB>
 ·Name Display            <SB>
 I explained Movement      <SB>
 Setttings before. It's    <SB>
 where you determine which <SB>
 buttons to use to walk    <SB>
 and run.                  <SB>
 Clock Display determines  <SB>
 whether or not the time and<SB>
 date is shown in the lower<SB>
 right hand corner when you<SB>
 are moving.               <SB>
 Face and Name Display     <SB>
 determines whether the name<SB>
 and face of the person you<SB>
 are talking to is shown in<SB>
 the Message Window.       <P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. Today I'll tell you  <SB>
 about controls in the     <SB>
 Diary from the            <SB>
 Menu Window.              <SB>
                           <SB>
 First, move the Control Pad<SB>
 Up and Down to move the   <SB>
 cursor up and down to     <SB>
 select a setting to change.<SB>
 Next, move the Control Pad<SB>
 Left and Right to change  <SB>
 the settings.             <SB>
 Press the B Button to close<SB>
 the Diary Window.         <SB>
 Also, press the A Button to<SB>
 save or load when those are<SB>
 selected.                 <SB>
That's about it for today."<SB>
"OK."                    <P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more  <SB>
 about the Menu Window.   <SB>
 Today's lesson will be on <SB>
 the Tools and Items       <SB>
 Screen.                   <SB>
                           <SB>
 The Tools and Item Screen <SB>
 shows what you have in    <SB>
 your Rucksack. You can also<SB>
 change what you're holding<SB>
 or equipped with here.    <SB>
 You can do this on the Map<SB>
 Screen, too, don't forget.<SB>
 This Screen is most useful<SB>
 for checking your         <SB>
 possessions."            <SB>
"I see."                 <P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more  <SB>
 about the Menu Window.   <SB>
 Today's lesson will be on <SB>
 the Tools and Items       <SB>
 Screen controls.          <SB>
                           <SB>
 Basically...              <SB>
 ·Control Pad: Move cursor<SB>
 ·A Button: Enter         <SB>
 ·B Button: Cancel        <SB>
 ·L/R Buttons: Move cursor<SB>
   between Tools and Items.<SB>
"That's easy enough!"    <SB>
"That's because you're my <SB>
 brother!"                <SB>
"Thanks, sis."           <P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more  <SB>
 about the Menu Window.   <SB>
 Today's lesson will be on <SB>
 the Town Map.             <SB>
                           <SB>
 On the Town Map Screen,   <SB>
 you can see a map of every-<SB>
 thing! Point your cursor at<SB>
 something to see an       <SB>
 explanation below."      <SB>
"That sounds pretty       <SB>
simple."                  <SB>
"Here's this, then:       <SB>
 The Control Pad moves the <SB>
 cursor, and the B Button  <SB>
 closes the Map Screen and <SB>
 returns you to the Menu   <SB>
 Window.                   <SB>
 Press the L Button to move<SB>
 the cursor more slowly,   <SB>
 and the R Button to       <SB>
 move it more quickly.     <SB>
 Got all that?"           <SB>
"I think so..."          <P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more  <SB>
 about the Menu Window.   <SB>
 Today's lesson will be on <SB>
 the Town Map.             <SB>
                           <SB>
 The Town Map also shows   <SB>
 where you and your Dog are.<SB>
 Also, it will show the    <SB>
 position of your Ball and <SB>
 Basket if you have them.  <SB>
 You can use this to help  <SB>
 you look for things you've<SB>
 lost.                     <SB>
 Of course, the map will   <SB>
 only show you the         <SB>
 approximate location, not <SB>
 exactly where it is. So,  <SB>
 you'll still have to do   <SB>
 some looking on your own. <SB>
 Also, if it's someone     <SB>
 else's house, the map can't<SB>
 show you what floor your  <SB>
 lost item is on."        <P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more  <SB>
 about the Menu Window.   <SB>
 Today's lesson will be on <SB>
 the Farm Map.             <SB>
                           <SB>
 The Farm Map Screen shows <SB>
 an overview of your farm. <SB>
 It's useful to look at when<SB>
 you forgot what you planted<SB>
 where, for instance."    <SB>
"That sounds pretty       <SB>
simple."                  <SB>
"Here's this, then:       <SB>
 The Control Pad moves the <SB>
 cursor, and the B Button  <SB>
 closes the Map Screen and <SB>
 returns you to the Menu   <SB>
 Window.                   <SB>
 Press the L Button to move<SB>
 the cursor more slowly,   <SB>
 and the R Button to       <SB>
 move it more quickly.     <SB>
 Got all that?"           <SB>
"I think so..."          <P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more  <SB>
 about the Menu Window.   <SB>
 Today's lesson will be on <SB>
 the Farm Map.             <SB>
                           <SB>
 On the Farm Map, you can  <SB>
 see the location of all   <SB>
 your animals in all the   <SB>
 buildings on your farm:   <SB>
 ·You, your Dog, your Ball,<SB>
   and Basket (if they're on<SB>
   the farm, that is)      <SB>
 ·Chickens, Baby Chicks,  <SB>
   Sheep, and Cows (if you <SB>
   have them)              <SB>
 ·Harvest Sprites         <SB>
   (if they're working     <SB>
   for you)                <SB>
                           <SB>
 That's about it."        <SB>
"Got it."                <P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more  <SB>
 about the Menu Window.   <SB>
 Today's lesson will be on <SB>
 your Earnings.            <SB>
                           <SB>
 The Earnings Screen is    <SB>
 divided up into many pages.<SB>
 The first one shows your  <SB>
 name, how much gold you   <SB>
 have, the number of       <SB>
 your animals, bushels of  <SB>
 Feed, and Lumber, and     <SB>
 the affection of your pet.<SB>
                           <SB>
 The next pages are animal <SB>
 list pages, one for       <SB>
 Chickens, Cows, and Sheep,<SB>
 If you have them. "<SB>
"So if have don't have    <SB>
 Sheep, then there will be <SB>
 no Sheep page?"          <SB>
"Exactly."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more  <SB>
 about the Menu Window.   <SB>
 Today's lesson will be    <SB>
 more on the Earnings      <SB>
 Screen.                   <SB>
                           <SB>
 Next page is the Harvest  <SB>
 Sprites page. This page   <SB>
 shows the affection of each<SB>
 Sprite for you, how much  <SB>
 their enthusiasm is for the<SB>
 job, and whether each is  <SB>
 doing a job for you or not.<SB>
 Job enthusiasm is shown   <SB>
 with a gauge, in the order<SB>
 of Watering, Harvest, and <SB>
 Animal Husbandry.         <SB>
                           <SB>
 The next page is your     <SB>
 Income and Expenses.      <SB>
 Income and Expenses for   <SB>
 this month is at the very <SB>
 top. Below that is your   <SB>
 daily Income and Expenses <SB>
 for the current season.   <SB>
 At the very bottom is your<SB>
 Income and Expenses for the<SB>
 last 3 seasons.           <SB>
 The last page shows the   <SB>
 levels of all your Tools."<SB>
"More tomorrow, right?"  <SB>
"Of course!"             <P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more  <SB>
 about the Menu Window.   <SB>
 Today's lesson will be    <SB>
 more on the Earnings      <SB>
 Screen.                   <SB>
                           <SB>
 Like I said yesterday, the<SB>
 final page on the Earnings<SB>
 screen shows the levels of<SB>
 all your Tools in numbers <SB>
 and a gauge.              <SB>
 When the gauge becomes    <SB>
 full, a small picture of an<SB>
 Ore will be shown below   <SB>
 that Tool. That ore tells <SB>
 you what level the Tool   <SB>
 can be upgraded to.       <SB>
 Remember that you don't   <SB>
 need to upgrade right away.<SB>
 You could wait to upgrade <SB>
 a Tool until it became    <SB>
 ready for a Mystrile      <SB>
 upgrade,                  <SB>
 if you wanted to!"       <SB>
"Yeah, but that would take<SB>
 forever!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more  <SB>
 about the Menu Window.   <SB>
 Today's lesson will be    <SB>
 more on the Earnings      <SB>
 Screen.                   <SB>
                           <SB>
 On the Tool Level List,   <SB>
 there is a number to the  <SB>
 right of each gauge.      <SB>
 This percentage shows     <SB>
 the experience level of the<SB>
 Tool. When it reaches 100%,<SB>
 the tool may be upgraded. <SB>
 To upgrade a Tool, bring  <SB>
 it to the blacksmith.     <SB>
 I'll tell you more about  <SB>
 the controls of this Screen<SB>
 tomorrow."               <SB>
"OK. Bye now."           <P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more  <SB>
 about the Menu Window.   <SB>
 Today's lesson will be    <SB>
 about controls in the     <SB>
 Earnings Screen.          <SB>
                           <SB>
 Flip pages with the Left  <SB>
 and Right Control Pad, and<SB>
 scroll with the Up and Down<SB>
 Control Pad.              <SB>
 Press the L Button with the<SB>
 Up and Down Control Pad to<SB>
 scroll more slowly, or    <SB>
 the R Button to scroll more<SB>
 quickly."                <SB>
"I think I've seen        <SB>
 instructions like these   <SB>
 before..."               <P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more  <SB>
 about the Menu Window.   <SB>
 Today's lesson will be    <SB>
 about the Memo Screen.    <SB>
                           <SB>
 The Memo helps you remember<SB>
 what you've done:         <SB>
 ·Number of shipments     <SB>
 ·Number of Fish caught   <SB>
 ·Other                   <SB>
There's one page for each."<SB>
"That's all?"            <SB>
"It's more than it looks  <SB>
 like at first glance.     <SB>
 For instance, there are   <SB>
 over 100 types of Items to<SB>
 be shipped, and many kinds<SB>
 of Fish to be caught.     <SB>
 The memo keeps track of   <SB>
 each individually, but I'll<SB>
 explain more tomorrow."  <SB>
"OK."                    <P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more  <SB>
 about the Menu Window.   <SB>
 Today's lesson will be    <SB>
 more about the Memo Screen.<SB>
                           <SB>
 I was going to tell you   <SB>
 even more about the Memo  <SB>
 Screen, but it doesn't have<SB>
 a direct bearing on game- <SB>
 play, so I decided against<SB>
 it. It's more fun that    <SB>
 way."                    <SB>
                           <SB>
"Awww, sis!... By the way,<SB>
 how high do the counters  <SB>
 for shipping and fishing  <SB>
 go...?"                  <SB>
"That's a secret! It sure <SB>
isn't 999. That much I can <SB>
say."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more  <SB>
 about the Menu Window.   <SB>
 Today's lesson will be    <SB>
 about the Memo Screen     <SB>
 controls.                 <SB>
                           <SB>
"Flip pages with the Left <SB>
 and Right Control Pad, and<SB>
 scroll with the Up and Down<SB>
 Control Pad.              <SB>
 Press the L Button with the<SB>
 Up and Down Control Pad to<SB>
 scroll more slowly, or    <SB>
 the R Button to scroll more<SB>
 quickly."                <SB>
"Are the controls for these<SB>
 Screens all the same?"   <SB>
"You catch on quick!"    <SB>
"I knew it!"             <P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"What will you teach me   <SB>
 about today?"            <SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 the Message Window.       <SB>
 The top left of the Message<SB>
 Window shows the face of  <SB>
 the person you're talking <SB>
 to, and the top right     <SB>
 shows their name."       <SB>
"It's not fair our names  <SB>
 and faces aren't shown!" <SB>
"...Maybe, but you can also<SB>
 choose not to display it."<SB>
"You mean in the Diary,   <SB>
 right?"                  <SB>
"Good memory. Actually,   <SB>
 you can change this when  <SB>
 the messages are shown,   <SB>
 too."                    <SB>
"You'll tell me how       <SB>
 tomorrow, right...?"     <P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more  <SB>
 about erasing the names and<SB>
 faces in the Message      <SB>
 Window."                 <SB>
"You were going to teach me<SB>
 how to do it without going<SB>
 to the Diary, right?"    <SB>
"Well, that's what I said,<SB>
 but it turns out I was    <SB>
 wrong.                    <SB>
 The Diary is the only place<SB>
 to do it. Sorry!..."     <SB>
"Thanks a lot, sis!"     <P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"What will you teach me   <SB>
 about today?"            <SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 things in your home       <SB>
 including some things you<SB>
 might not have yet.      <SB>
 The first is the Bed.     <SB>
 This doesn't need very much<SB>
 explanation, I know.      <SB>
 Just investigate it,      <SB>
 and you wake up the next  <SB>
 morning."                <SB>
"But, why can't I just work<SB>
 on the farm until morning <SB>
 comes? I can save at any  <SB>
 time, right?"            <SB>
"You'll collapse if you   <SB>
 work like that!"         <SB>
"Really?"                <SB>
"I'll explain more later."<SB>
"Bye now."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. I was saying that if <SB>
 you don't get enough sleep,<SB>
 you'll end up collapsing. <SB>
 If you use any Tool, you  <SB>
 lose a bit of Stamina.    <SB>
 If you run out of Stamina,<SB>
 you collapse.             <SB>
 That's not such a big deal.<SB>
 But, if you keep on using <SB>
 a Tool when you have no   <SB>
 Stamina, you'll build up  <SB>
 Fatigue.                  <SB>
 If you build up Fatigue   <SB>
 until you collapse, you'll<SB>
 be carried to the Clinic. <SB>
 It takes a full day to    <SB>
 recover then!"           <SB>
"What does that have to do<SB>
 with not sleeping?"      <SB>
"I'll explain it          <SB>
tomorrow."                <SB>
"OK..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. I was saying that if <SB>
 you don't get enough sleep,<SB>
 you'll end up collapsing. <SB>
 If you don't get sleep,   <SB>
 Fatigue builds up.        <SB>
 So, even if you don't do  <SB>
 any work, you'll end up   <SB>
 being carried to the Clinic<SB>
 if you stay up all night."<SB>
"Don't you recuperate     <SB>
 Stamina and Fatigue?"    <SB>
"You do, if you:          <SB>
 ·Eat food                <SB>
 ·Enter a Hot Spring      <SB>
 ·Sleep                   <SB>
 There are other ways to   <SB>
 recuperate as well, but   <SB>
 I'll tell you about them  <SB>
 later."                  <SB>
"OK. You build up Fatigue <SB>
 when you use Tools when   <SB>
 your Stamina is drained,  <SB>
 or when you don't sleep,  <SB>
 right?"<SB>
"Right."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"Teach me more from       <SB>
 yesterday!"              <SB>
"OK. I'll teach you about <SB>
 how you build up Fatigue. <SB>
 Aside from what I told you<SB>
 yesterday, you also build <SB>
 up Fatigue when you use a <SB>
 Tool either in the rain   <SB>
 or late at night.         <SB>
 Also, I forgot to tell you<SB>
 that some foods can       <SB>
 drain your Stamina and    <SB>
 cause Fatigue."          <SB>
"What food could do       <SB>
that?!"                   <SB>
"Two things are Poison    <SB>
 Mushrooms, or failed      <SB>
 dishes. There are some    <SB>
 others, too."            <SB>
"I'd better be careful!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"What will you teach me   <SB>
 about today?"            <SB>
"Today I'll teach you more<SB>
 about things in your home <SB>
 (including some things you<SB>
 might not have yet).      <SB>
 Now I'll explain the      <SB>
 Diary. This is the same   <SB>
 as the Diary in the Menu  <SB>
 Window. You can use it    <SB>
 to save or load games, or <SB>
 make various settings."  <SB>
"Wouldn't it just be easier<SB>
 to use START and go to    <SB>
 the Diary from the Menu   <SB>
 Window...?"              <SB>
"Sometimes people just like<SB>
 a change of pace,         <SB>
 that's all!"             <SB>
"If you say so..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"What will you teach me   <SB>
 about today?"            <SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 the Calendar.             <SB>
 It's useful for finding out<SB>
about the season's events."<SB>
"How do you use it?"     <SB>
"Investigate it to display<SB>
 the Calendar Screen.      <SB>
 Use the Control Pad to move<SB>
 the cursor to the day you <SB>
 want to check, then press <SB>
 the A Button.             <SB>
 The Message Window will   <SB>
 show what's planned then. <SB>
 Use the B Button to step  <SB>
 back from the Calendar.   <SB>
 Oh yeah, days with events <SB>
 on them have a helpful    <SB>
 symbol on them."         <SB>
"Thanks. Very useful!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"What will you teach me   <SB>
 about today?"            <SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 the TV.                   <SB>
 You can use the TV to watch<SB>
 many interesting programs.<SB>
 The Control Pad is your   <SB>
 remote control:           <SB>
 ·Up: Weather forecast    <SB>
 ·Down: This program      <SB>
 ·Right: News             <SB>
 ·Left: Variety programs  <SB>
 You can change channels at<SB>
 any time, do don't feel   <SB>
 like you have to watch the<SB>
 whole thing.              <SB>
 The B Button turns the TV <SB>
 off, and the other buttons<SB>
 fast forward the messages.<SB>
That's all there is to it!"<SB>
"Easy enough, I guess."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"What will you teach me   <SB>
 about today?"            <SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 different TV programs.    <SB>
 First is the Weather      <SB>
 forecast. It's usually    <SB>
 fairly accurate, so make  <SB>
 a habit of checking it    <SB>
 every morning when you    <SB>
 wake up.                  <SB>
 Next is the News, which   <SB>
 tells you what events are <SB>
 going on this season.     <SB>
 The day before or the day <SB>
 of an event, the news     <SB>
 sometimes covers that     <SB>
 event only. So, it's a    <SB>
 good idea to remember     <SB>
 events as much as you     <SB>
can." "I see."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"What will you teach me   <SB>
 about today?"            <SB>
"Today I'll teach you more<SB>
 about TV Stations.        <SB>
 Life on the Farm is this  <SB>
 program, so it needs no   <SB>
 description.              <SB>
 A different Variety program<SB>
 is on each day of the week:<SB>
 ·Sunday: My Dear Princess<SB>
 ·Monday: Fishing Hour    <SB>
 ·Tuesday: Dueling Chefs  <SB>
 ·Wednesday: Aaron Changes<SB>
 ·Thursday: Star Lilly,   <SB>
   Bandit Girl             <SB>
 ·Friday: Mechabot Ultror <SB>
 ·Saturday: TV Shopping   <SB>
   Network or St. Emerald  <SB>
   Academy                 <SB>
Well, that's it for today!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"What will you teach me   <SB>
 about today?"            <SB>
"Today I'll teach you more<SB>
 about TV Stations.        <SB>
 "Fishing Hour" has      <SB>
 information about fishing,<SB>
 and "Dueling Chefs" has <SB>
 information about cooking.<SB>
 You might find them       <SB>
 useful.                   <SB>
 The TV Shopping Network   <SB>
 is where you order a whole<SB>
 lot of stuff, so it's very<SB>
 useful.                   <SB>
 The other programs are just<SB>
 there fore your enjoyment.<SB>
 They don't really have a  <SB>
 specific purpose. "      <SB>
"I see..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"What will you teach me   <SB>
 about today?"            <SB>
"Today I'll teach you more<SB>
 about TV Stations.        <SB>
 They stop broadcasting    <SB>
 late at night; midnight   <SB>
 to be exact.              <SB>
 Also, the signal won't come<SB>
 through on stormy days." <SB>
"So I can't watch TV      <SB>
 then?"                   <SB>
"No, you just have to get <SB>
 rest and wait for the next<SB>
 day to start."           <SB>
"That's too bad!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 your Bookshelf.<SB>
 The Bookshelf is where you<SB>
 keep Books or Letters you<SB>
 have already read.<SB>
 If you investigate the<SB>
 Bookshelf, you can select<SB>
 between View Books or<SB>
 View Letters. You can then<SB>
 choose which one to read.<SB>
 You won't have any Letters<SB>
 at the very beginning, but<SB>
 check your Mailbox for<SB>
 them.<SB>
 You do start out with some<SB>
 Books, and you'll get <SB>
 more over time."<SB>
"I see."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 your Tool Box.<SB>
 This is where you can keep<SB>
 all your Tools. 8 fit on<SB>
 each page, and there are<SB>
 8 pages, so you can have<SB>
 64 kinds Tools in all. You<SB>
 can hold up to 99 of each<SB>
 kind of Tool.<SB>
 This is useful for things<SB>
 like Seeds, which you need<SB>
 to stock for next year."<SB>
"If I have enough gold to<SB>
 stock up, that is!"<SB>
"The first year could be<SB>
 tough, but..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 your Refrigerator.<SB>
 It's where you keep<SB>
 Ingredients for cooking.<SB>
 Just like the Tool Box,<SB>
 you can fit 99 of each<SB>
 kind of Item. This is<SB>
 much more than what<SB>
 your Rucksack holds.<SB>
 Also, this time you won't<SB>
 get a Refrigerator just by<SB>
 expanding your home.<SB>
 You'll need to buy it on<SB>
 the TV Shopping Network.<SB>
 Expanding your home is a<SB>
 little cheaper than last<SB>
 time, but you have to pay<SB>
 for the Refrigerator,<SB>
 so the whole process ends<SB>
 up costing little more."<SB>
"OK. I see."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 your Shelf.<SB>
 This is where you keep<SB>
 Items that aren't for<SB>
 cooking.<SB>
 Just like the Tool Box,<SB>
 you can fit 99 of each<SB>
 kind of Item. This is<SB>
 much more than what<SB>
 your Rucksack holds.<SB>
 Also, this time you won't<SB>
 get a Shelf either just by<SB>
 expanding your home.<SB>
 You'll need to buy it on<SB>
 the TV Shopping Network.<SB>
 Expanding your home is a<SB>
 little cheaper than last<SB>
 time, but you have to pay<SB>
 for the Shelf,<SB>
 so the whole process ends<SB>
 up costing little more."<SB>
"OK. I see."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 controls for your Shelf"<SB>
 and Refrigerator.<SB>
 Basically:<SB>
 ·Control Pad: Move cursor<SB>
 ·A Button: Enter<SB>
 ·B Button: Cancel<SB>
 ·L/R Buttons: Move cursor<SB>
   between Items, Shelf, and<SB>
   Refrigerator Screens.<SB>
 The controls are a lot<SB>
 like the Tools and Items<SB>
 Screen. Also, select an<SB>
 Item and then press START<SB>
 to throw it away."<SB>
"Why would you do that?"<SB>
"If you wanted to throw<SB>
away all 99 of one kind of<SB>
Item, for instance."<SB>
"Hmm...It must be tough<SB>
 deciding what to keep<SB>
 and what to throw away."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 the Kitchen.<SB>
 You can't cook unless you<SB>
 have a Kitchen. Of course,<SB>
 you'll also need Utensils<SB>
 to make most things.<SB>
 Buy both Kitchen and<SB>
 Utensils on the TV Shopping<SB>
 Network.<SB>
 You can't buy Utensils<SB>
 until you have a Kitchen,<SB>
 and you can't buy a Kitchen<SB>
 unless you have a<SB>
 Refrigerator and Shelves.<SB>
 I'll cover Utensils more<SB>
 tomorrow."<SB>
"OK."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 your Utensils.<SB>
 There are 8 Utensils:<SB>
 ·Knife<SB>
 ·Frying Pan<SB>
 ·Pot<SB>
 ·Mixer<SB>
 ·Whisk<SB>
 ·Rolling Pin<SB>
 ·Oven<SB>
 ·Seasoning Set<SB>
 You'll need different<SB>
 Utensils to cook each<SB>
 recipe. You can learn<SB>
 recipes by experimenting<SB>
 yourself, by talking to<SB>
 people in town, or by<SB>
 watching TV."<SB>
"Somehow I don't think I'd<SB>
 be too successful<SB>
 experimenting..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 cooking.<SB>
 First, enter your Kitchen<SB>
 without holding anything."<SB>
"Why not?"<SB>
"Because you'll end up<SB>
 holding what you make.<SB>
 When you enter the Kitchen,<SB>
 you'll have these choices:<SB>
 ·Cook<SB>
 ·View Recipes<SB>
 ·Exit<SB>
 First I'll explain Cook.<SB>
 When you select it, you'll<SB>
 see the Utensil Window.<SB>
 We're out of time today, so<SB>
 I'll finish tomorrow."<SB>
"I hate waiting!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more<SB>
 about the Utensil Window<SB>
 when you select Cook in<SB>
 the Kitchen. The controls<SB>
 are basically like other<SB>
 screens. But, things change<SB>
 a bit when you select<SB>
 Seasoning Set and the<SB>
 Seasoning Window appears."<SB>
"That's where I can choose<SB>
 to use Sugar, Salt,<SB>
 Vinegar, Soy Sauce, or<SB>
 Miso, right?"<SB>
"Right. Don't use them<SB>
 indiscriminately, though,<SB>
 or your dish won't turn out<SB>
 well at all!<SB>
 Once you select Seasonings,<SB>
 you'll move to the<SB>
 Ingredient Window. I'll<SB>
 explain that tomorrow."<SB>
"Aww...Not more waiting!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more<SB>
 about what happens when<SB>
 you investigate the<SB>
 Kitchen, select Cook, then<SB>
 select Seasonings<SB>
 to use.<SB>
 The Ingredient Window<SB>
 opens, which is where you<SB>
 choose which Ingredients to<SB>
 use from the Refrigerator<SB>
 or your Rucksack."<SB>
"Can I choose anything?<SB>
 Even things in my Rucksack<SB>
 that aren't edible?"<SB>
"You can, but no guarantees<SB>
 on how it'll turn out!<SB>
 The controls are like the<SB>
 other screens.<SB>
 Once you've chosen at least<SB>
 one Ingredient, press START<SB>
 to move to the Utensil<SB>
 Window."<SB>
"More tomorrow, right?"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more<SB>
 about cooking. After<SB>
 investigating the Kitchen<SB>
 and selecting Cook, then<SB>
 choosing Utensils and<SB>
 Ingredients, you have the<SB>
 following choice:<SB>
 ·Use these Ingredients<SB>
 ·Restart from Ingredients<SB>
 ·Restart from Utensils<SB>
 The bottom two are easy<SB>
 to understand. The first<SB>
 one starts the actual<SB>
 cooking, and what comes<SB>
 next depends on what<SB>
 the outcome is.<SB>
 I'll explain it tomorrow."<SB>
"Not again..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more<SB>
 about what happens when<SB>
 you cook something.<SB>
 If the recipe doesn't work,<SB>
 you'll get a message<SB>
 telling about your failure.<SB>
 If it was your first time<SB>
 making something, you'll<SB>
 get a message offering to<SB>
 write down the recipe.<SB>
 If you make a dish exactly<SB>
 the same way you made it<SB>
 before, you'll get a<SB>
 message telling you it's<SB>
 been made.<SB>
 Finally, if you make the<SB>
 same dish but change it,<SB>
 you'll get a message<SB>
 offering to rewrite the<SB>
 recipe."<SB>
"Is that it for now?"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you more<SB>
 about cooking.<SB>
 When you investigate the<SB>
 Kitchen and then select<SB>
 View Recipes, you'll see a<SB>
 list of recipes you've made<SB>
 before.<SB>
 Of course, you won't see<SB>
 this if you've never made<SB>
 anything successfully.<SB>
 Once you see the list, use<SB>
 the cursor and the A<SB>
 Button to select the dish<SB>
 you want to make.<SB>
 The next message depends<SB>
 on whether or not you<SB>
 have all the right<SB>
 Ingredients."<SB>
"Let me guess: More on that<SB>
 tomorrow, right...?"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"OK. I'll teach you more<SB>
 about what happens after<SB>
 you choose to make a<SB>
 recipe you've already<SB>
 made before.<SB>
 If you have all the right<SB>
 Ingredients, you'll see the<SB>
 following choice:<SB>
 ·Follow the recipe<SB>
 ·Improvise recipe<SB>
 ·Make another recipe<SB>
 The first option makes<SB>
 the dish.<SB>
 The second option will<SB>
 bring you back to the<SB>
 Utensil Window, remembering<SB>
 the Utensils for the recipe<SB>
 and the Ingredients you've<SB>
 chosen.<SB>
 The third option will<SB>
 bring you back to the<SB>
 recipe selection screen.<SB>
 That's it for today."<SB>
"How much more is<SB>
there...?"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"OK. I'll teach you about<SB>
 what happens when you don't<SB>
 have all the Ingredients<SB>
 for the recipe you've<SB>
 chosen to make. The<SB>
 selection will be:<SB>
 ·Improvise recipe<SB>
 ·Make another recipe<SB>
 The first option will<SB>
 bring you back to the<SB>
 Utensil Window, remembering<SB>
 the Utensils for the recipe<SB>
 and the Ingredients you've<SB>
 chosen.<SB>
 The second option will<SB>
 bring you back to the<SB>
 recipe selection screen.<SB>
 That's it for today."<SB>
"We're done with cooking<SB>
 now, right...?"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 the Clock.<SB>
 You have to buy it from<SB>
 the TV Shopping Network."<SB>
"Does it just tell the<SB>
 time...that's all?"<SB>
"What's wrong with that?"<SB>
"But you can see the time<SB>
 anyway, in the bottom right<SB>
 corner of the screen!"<SB>
"Some people just like to<SB>
 keep Clocks in their house,<SB>
 OK?! Consider it fashion."<SB>
"Whatever you say, sis..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 the Mirror.<SB>
 It will tell you messages<SB>
 when you look in it, but<SB>
 it serves no real purpose.<SB>
 It's basically just for<SB>
 looks. Buy it from the<SB>
 TV Shopping Network when<SB>
 you have extra money."<SB>
"I don't think that'll<SB>
 be anytime soon..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 the Vase."<SB>
 You can use it to hold<SB>
 flowers."<SB>
"Does that do any good?"<SB>
"It does! Flowers will help<SB>
 you recuperate Stamina and<SB>
 Fatigue in the morning when<SB>
 you wake up.<SB>
 Just how much depends on<SB>
 the kind of flower.<SB>
 Also, flowers will wilt<SB>
 quickly if you don't use<SB>
 them in the right season.<SB>
 The wandering salesman<SB>
 Won will come by once in<SB>
 a while to sell you<SB>
 the Vase."<SB>
"Got it, sis."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you how<SB>
to use your Vase."<SB>
 All you have to do is<SB>
 investigate the Vase while<SB>
 holding a bunch of flowers<SB>
 to put them in it.<SB>
 If there are already some<SB>
 in the Vase, you'll throw<SB>
 them away automatically,<SB>
 so be careful. You'll be<SB>
 asked for confirmation,<SB>
 though, so don't worry<SB>
 about it too much."<SB>
"I see."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 the Fireplace."<SB>
 You'll get one when you add<SB>
 a second floor to your<SB>
 home.<SB>
 Throw Branches or Lumber<SB>
 on it to start a fire and<SB>
 cheer up your home."<SB>
"Why does just throwing<SB>
 wood in the Fireplace start<SB>
 the fire, sis?"<SB>
"Never mind the small<SB>
 stuff! The important thing<SB>
 is that your home will heat<SB>
 up, which will recuperate<SB>
 Stamina in Winter but<SB>
 cause it in all other<SB>
 seasons."<SB>
"Got it."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 the Carpet.<SB>
 You can buy it from the<SB>
 TV Shopping Network to<SB>
 put in your home.<SB>
 It really does serve no<SB>
 purpose other than<SB>
 decoration, though."<SB>
"So you really don't need<SB>
 to buy it at all?..."<SB>
"Maybe when you have<SB>
 extra money."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 the Large Bed.<SB>
 It's really just a larger<SB>
 Bed than your first one."<SB>
"So it doesn't have any<SB>
 use, either?"<SB>
 "You can't get married<SB>
 without a Large Bed. That's<SB>
 where your wife sleeps."<SB>
"Why does she get the Large<SB>
 Bed?"<SB>
"That's where she'll sleep<SB>
 with your child when it's<SB>
 born."<SB>
"That seems awfully far<SB>
 away..."<SB>
"Just remember this when<SB>
 you want to get married."<SB>
"If you say so."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 the Bath.<SB>
 You can't order a Bath<SB>
 until you add a second<SB>
 floor to your house.<SB>
 Once you do, you'll be able<SB>
 to bathe at home."<SB>
"You mean like the Hot<SB>
 Spring at Mother's Hill?"<SB>
"Yes. If you enter your<SB>
 Bath for 30 minutes at <SB>
 home, you'll recuperate<SB>
 Stamina and Fatigue.<SB>
 (If you enter the bath<SB>
 between 5:30-6AM, you'll be<SB>
 forced to get out at 6AM.<SB>
 The health effects aren't<SB>
 as large as at the Hot<SB>
 Spring, but it's nice to<SB>
 have in your own home."<SB>
"Yes, it sounds relaxing."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 the Sock hook."<SB>
"What's that?"<SB>
"On the wall to the left of<SB>
 the Bookshelf, there is a<SB>
 place to hang a Sock.<SB>
 This is the Sock hook.<SB>
 If you hang a Sock here<SB>
 on the 25th of Winter,<SB>
 someone may give you a<SB>
 gift.<SB>
 But, Socks aren't sold any-<SB>
 where, so you have to get<SB>
 someone to make you one.<SB>
 You'll need Yarn for that,<SB>
 though..."<SB>
"I didn't know about<SB>
that!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 the Record Player.<SB>
 They sell them someplace,<SB>
 but I've never seen one<SB>
 around here. Put a Record<SB>
 on it to play music."<SB>
"That sounds pretty<SB>
 obvious to me!"<SB>
"Give me a break, will<SB>
ya?"<SB>
"Sorry, sis..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 your farm buildings.<SB>
 First is the Shipment box.<SB>
 Put shippable Items here,<SB>
 and in the evening<SB>
 the shipper will come to<SB>
 pick it up and leave you<SB>
 money."<SB>
"How do you know what's<SB>
 shippable?"<SB>
"You can't even put things<SB>
 that aren't shippable in<SB>
 the Shipment box, so<SB>
 you'll figure it out."<SB>
"You're not very helpful,<SB>
 sometimes!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 the Mailbox.<SB>
 Investigate it to see if<SB>
 you have any new letters.<SB>
 It's a good idea to<SB>
 check it once in a while,<SB>
 since you never know when<SB>
 a letter will arrive!<SB>
 Letters are put away in the<SB>
 Bookshelf once you've read<SB>
 them, so go there to<SB>
 read them again.<SB>
 If you get two ore more<SB>
 identical letters, only<SB>
 one will remain in your<SB>
 Bookshelf."<SB>
"I see."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 the Doghouse."<SB>
"What good is the<SB>
 Doghouse?" It has your<SB>
 Dog's name on it, but your<SB>
 Dog doesn't sleep there.<SB>
 Especially in the rain,<SB>
 when you should let him in<SB>
 your house.<SB>
 I really don't know what<SB>
 good it is at all..."<SB>
"It might not be useful,<SB>
 but I like it!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 the Tree.<SB>
 There's a Bee Nest in the<SB>
 Tree, and you can<SB>
 investigate it once a day<SB>
 to find Honey."<SB>
"Only once a day?"<SB>
"They can only make so<SB>
 much!"<SB>
 Also, in Fall Apples will<SB>
 fall, so you should pick<SB>
 them up everyday.<SB>
 You can eat them straight<SB>
 or use them for cooking."<SB>
"If I don't have a<SB>
 Refrigerator, I probably<SB>
 shouldn't pick too many."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 the Water Mill.<SB>
 If you face the Mill and<SB>
 throw Corn in, you'll<SB>
 make 30 bushels of Chicken<SB>
 Feed. If you compare the<SB>
 price of Chicken Feed and<SB>
 the price of Corn, you'll<SB>
 see it's cheaper to make<SB>
 the Feed yourself. But,<SB>
 it's a close call.<SB>
 It's always good to<SB>
 remember if you run out of<SB>
 Feed and the Poultry Farm<SB>
 is closed."<SB>
"I see."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 your Woodbin.<SB>
 If you chop up Stumps or<SB>
 Branches with your Axe,<SB>
 they will automatically go<SB>
 in the Woodbin. So does<SB>
 Lumber when you buy it<SB>
 from Gotz.<SB>
 If you want to take out<SB>
 Lumber, just investigate<SB>
 the Woodbin when you<SB>
 aren't holding anything.<SB>
 To put Lumber you're<SB>
 holding in, just<SB>
 investigate as well."<SB>
"OK."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 your Stable.<SB>
 It's where you keep your<SB>
 Horse."<SB>
"But I don't have one in<SB>
 the beginning, right?"<SB>
"That's right. But this is<SB>
 the only place a Horse<SB>
 can go. Remember, you<SB>
 have to keep your Horse<SB>
 (and all other animals)<SB>
 inside on rainy or snowy<SB>
 days."<SB>
"I'll remember."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 your Barn.<SB>
 The Barn is where you keep<SB>
 you Cows and Sheep.<SB>
 It's where they come when<SB>
 you buy them from Yodel<SB>
 Farm.<SB>
 You can also put<SB>
 Chickens in here, but<SB>
 you can't give them Chicken<SB>
 Feed in a Barn. So, you<SB>
 should always keep them in<SB>
 the Chicken Coop.<SB>
 Inside the Barn, there is:<SB>
 ·Feed Bin Door<SB>
 ·Feed Boxes<SB>
 ·Shipment box<SB>
 I'll explain these<SB>
 tomorrow."<SB>
"OK."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you more<SB>
 about your Barn.<SB>
 First is the Feed Bin Door.<SB>
 This is where you get<SB>
 Fodder kept in the Feed<SB>
 Bin. You have to carry<SB>
 the bushels of Fodder back,<SB>
 so you have to have empty<SB>
 hands, remember.<SB>
 You can also put back<SB>
 bushels you won't use here.<SB>
 You can get Fodder either<SB>
 by cutting grass on your<SB>
 farm or at Yodel Farm."<SB>
"Got it!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you more<SB>
 about your Barn.<SB>
 Want to learn about Feed<SB>
 Boxes? Place Fodder here to<SB>
 feed the Cows and Sheep in<SB>
 the Barn."<SB>
"The grazing Cows and Sheep<SB>
won't eat from Feed Boxes?"<SB>
"Exactly. They'll find<SB>
grass to eat on their own.<SB>
 So, you have to think of<SB>
 just how many animals are<SB>
 in the Barn. If you put in<SB>
 too many bushels of Fodder,<SB>
 it will disappear the next<SB>
 day and go to waste."<SB>
"Got it."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you more<SB>
 about your Barn.<SB>
 This lesson will be about<SB>
 the Barn Shipment Box.<SB>
 This is the exactly like<SB>
 the one outside your house.<SB>
 The shipping guy will come<SB>
 everyday to pick up what<SB>
 you have to sell.<SB>
 He'll leave the right<SB>
 amount of gold, which is<SB>
 the same whichever Shipment<SB>
 box you use.<SB>
"That makes it easier to<SB>
 ship things like Milk,<SB>
 right?"<SB>
"That's the idea."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 expanding your Barn.<SB>
 Before Barn expansion, you<SB>
 can only keep 8 Cows and<SB>
 Sheep total, but afterwards<SB>
 you'll have room for 16!"<SB>
"In whatever combination I<SB>
 want?"<SB>
"Yes, you could keep 8 of<SB>
 each, or 16 Sheep, for<SB>
 instance.<SB>
 There are also some things<SB>
 you can't buy until you<SB>
 expand. I'll explain about<SB>
 that tomorrow."<SB>
"OK..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 things you can't put in<SB>
 your Barn until you expand.<SB>
 First is the Cheese Maker.<SB>
 You can get the black-<SB>
 smith to make this for you.<SB>
 When you do, just throw<SB>
 Milk in and it becomes<SB>
 Cheese!"<SB>
"What kind of cheese?"<SB>
"Never mind that! What<SB>
 matters is that the more<SB>
 Milk you put in, the more<SB>
 Cheese comes out.<SB>
 Next is the Yarn Maker.<SB>
 The blacksmith makes this,<SB>
 too. Throw in Wool to<SB>
 make Yarn. The larger<SB>
 size Wool you put in,<SB>
 the larger size Yarn comes<SB>
 out.<SB>
 That's it for the Barn."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 your Chicken Coop.<SB>
 Just as you'd guess, it's<SB>
 where you keep your<SB>
 Chickens.<SB>
 When you buy Chickens from<SB>
 Yodel Farm, they're put in<SB>
 the Chicken Coop.<SB>
 Cows and Sheep are just<SB>
 too big to fit in the<SB>
 doorway.<SB>
 The Chicken Coop contains:<SB>
 ·Chicken Feed Bin Door<SB>
 ·Feed Boxes<SB>
 ·Incubator<SB>
 ·Shipment box<SB>
 I'll explain more<SB>
 tomorrow."<SB>
"OK."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you more<SB>
 about your Chicken Coop.<SB>
 First is the Chicken Feed<SB>
 Bin Door.<SB>
 This is where you get<SB>
 Chicken Feed kept in the<SB>
 Feed Bin. You have to carry<SB>
 the Chicken Feed back,<SB>
 so you have to have empty<SB>
 hands, remember.<SB>
 You can also put back<SB>
 Feed you don't use here.<SB>
 You can buy Chicken Feed<SB>
 from Yodel Farm, or make<SB>
 it yourself at the Water<SB>
 Mill."<SB>
"Got it."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you more<SB>
 about your Chicken Coop.<SB>
 Want to learn about Feed<SB>
 Boxes? Place Chicken Feed<SB>
 here to feed the Chickens<SB>
 in the Chicken Coop."<SB>
"The Chickens grazing<SB>
won't eat from Feed Boxes?"<SB>
"Exactly. They'll find<SB>
 stuff to eat on their own.<SB>
 So, you have to think of<SB>
 just how many Chickens are<SB>
 in the Coop. If you give<SB>
 them too much Chicken Feed,<SB>
 it will disappear the next<SB>
 day and go to waste."<SB>
 By the way, Chicks don't<SB>
 need to be fed at all."<SB>
"Got it."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you more<SB>
 about your Chicken Coop.<SB>
 How about the Incubator?<SB>
 Place Eggs here and they<SB>
 will hatch into Chicks in<SB>
 3 days.<SB>
 Just hold an Egg and<SB>
 investigate the Incubator<SB>
 to put it in.<SB>
 Only one Egg at a time<SB>
 fits. Also, all baby Chicks<SB>
 are born the same, no<SB>
 matter what kind of Eggs<SB>
 you use."<SB>
"Interesting..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you more<SB>
 about your Chicken Coop.<SB>
 This lesson will be about<SB>
 the Shipment box.<SB>
 This is the exactly like<SB>
 the one outside your house.<SB>
 The shipping guy will come<SB>
 everyday to pick up what<SB>
 you have to sell.<SB>
 He'll leave the right<SB>
 amount of gold, which is<SB>
 the same whichever Shipment<SB>
 box you use.<SB>
"So it's just like the one<SB>
 in the Barn too, right?"<SB>
"That's the idea."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 expanding the Chicken Coop.<SB>
 Before expanding your<SB>
 Chicken Coop, you only<SB>
 have room for 4 Chickens.<SB>
 After expanding, though,<SB>
 you'll have room for 8!<SB>
"8 Chickens could sure lay<SB>
 a lot of Eggs!"<SB>
"Indeed. There is also<SB>
 something you can't buy<SB>
 until you expand. I'll<SB>
 explain about it<SB>
tomorrow." "OK..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 what you can't put in<SB>
 your Chicken Coop<SB>
 until you expand.<SB>
 It's the Mayonnaise Maker!<SB>
 You can ask the black-<SB>
 smith to make it for you.<SB>
 Just throw in some Eggs to<SB>
 make delicious Mayonnaise!<SB>
 The larger the Eggs you put<SB>
 in, the more Mayo will<SB>
 come out."<SB>
"All this sounds an awful<SB>
 lot like what you said<SB>
 about the Barn..."<SB>
"I can't help it if<SB>
 they're the same, can I?"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"Today I'll teach you about<SB>
 water drawing spots.<SB>
 These are places you can<SB>
 fill your Watering Can.<SB>
 The closest one is the pond<SB>
 below the Shipment box.<SB>
 It doesn't have to be<SB>
 there, though.<SB>
 You can draw water from<SB>
 anywhere, like the river<SB>
 or lake.<SB>
 You might find the pond<SB>
 most convenient for<SB>
 watering crops though."<SB>
"Sounds good to me."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"From now on I'll teach you<SB>
 about places outside<SB>
 your farm.<SB>
 First is the Hot Spring on<SB>
 Mother's Hill.<SB>
 Bathing in the Hot Spring<SB>
 recuperates Stamina and<SB>
 Fatigue."<SB>
"By how much?"<SB>
"The longer you stay in,<SB>
 the better. You can't get<SB>
 better than your maximum<SB>
 Stamina, or reduce your<SB>
 Fatigue below 0, though."<SB>
"Can I go on rainy days?"<SB>
"Sure. Weather doesn't<SB>
 matter at all."<SB>
"Great!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"How about the mine on<SB>
 Mother's Hill?<SB>
 In the mine, you can:<SB>
·Dig the ground with a Hoe<SB>
·Smash Stones with a Hammer<SB>
 By digging the ground,<SB>
 you'll be able to find<SB>
 stairs going downward or<SB>
 various grasses.<SB>
 By smashing Rocks, you'll<SB>
 be able to find Ores.<SB>
 The deeper you go in the<SB>
 mine, the more valuable<SB>
 things you'll find."<SB>
"How far down can you go?"<SB>
"I don't know...At least 10<SB>
 levels below ground."<SB>
"I bet I could go<SB>
farther!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"How about the<SB>
 Woodcutter's? House in the<SB>
 forest? Gotz lives there.<SB>
 You can buy Lumber from<SB>
 him, or ask him to to<SB>
 expand your farm.<SB>
 If you buy Lumber, he'll<SB>
 deliver it straight to your<SB>
 Woodbin, so you don't<SB>
 have to worry about it.<SB>
 If you ask him to expand<SB>
 something on your farm,<SB>
 he'll start the next day.<SB>
 It takes him 3 days to<SB>
 finish a project.<SB>
 You can't change your mind<SB>
 once you ask him, and he<SB>
 only works on one thing<SB>
 at a time.<SB>
 Oh, I forgot:<SB>
 You have to talk to Gotz<SB>
 behind the counter at his<SB>
 store. This is the same for<SB>
 all the other stores,<SB>
too." "I'll remember."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"How about the Poultry<SB>
 Farm in south Mineral Town?<SB>
 Here you can:<SB>
 ·Buy or sell Chickens<SB>
 ·Buy Chicken Feed<SB>
 ·Buy Animal Medicine<SB>
 The first thing you have to<SB>
 do when you buy a Chicken<SB>
 is name it, so think of a<SB>
 good name beforehand.<SB>
 When selling a Chicken,<SB>
 you get to select which of<SB>
 your Chickens you want to<SB>
 sell. You can't sell baby<SB>
 Chicks.<SB>
 I'll explain about buying<SB>
 Chicken Feed tomorrow."<SB>
"OK. I'll wait."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"I was talking about the<SB>
 Poultry Farm, right?"<SB>
 Just like with buying<SB>
 Lumber from Gotz, when you<SB>
 buy Chicken Feed from the<SB>
 Poultry Farm, it is shipped<SB>
 directly to your Chicken<SB>
 Feed Bin. You don't need to<SB>
 worry about carrying it.<SB>
 Animal Medicine is<SB>
 considered a Tool to be<SB>
 equipped, so you can put it<SB>
 in your Rucksack.<SB>
 If it's full it will be<SB>
 shipped directly to your<SB>
 Tool Box."<SB>
"What if the Tool Box is<SB>
 full, sis?"<SB>
"You'll be told that<SB>
 there's no room for it, so<SB>
 you can't buy it.<SB>
 This is true for all Tools,<SB>
 actually."<SB>
"I see."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"How about Yodel<SB>
 Farm in south Mineral Town?<SB>
 Here you can:<SB>
 ·Buy or Sell Cows and Sheep<SB>
 ·Buy Animal Fodder<SB>
 ·Buy Animal Medicine<SB>
 ·Buy Cow or Sheep<SB>
   Miracle Potion<SB>
 ·Buy a Bell<SB>
 When you buy a Cow or a<SB>
 Sheep, the first thing you<SB>
 do is name it, so think of<SB>
 a good name first.<SB>
 I'll explain the rest<SB>
 tomorrow."<SB>
"There is awful lot to buy<SB>
 here, isn't there?"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"I was talking about<SB>
 Yodel Farm, right?"<SB>
 When you want to sell a<SB>
 Cow or a Sheep, a list of<SB>
 your animals will appear.<SB>
 Just choose from that.<SB>
 By the way, you can only<SB>
 sell fully grown animals.<SB>
 Also, when you buy Animal<SB>
 Fodder, it's delivered<SB>
 straight to your Feed Bin,<SB>
 so you don't have to worry<SB>
 about carrying it.<SB>
 Animal Medicine and Bells<SB>
 are considered Tools,<SB>
 so when you buy them<SB>
 they're placed in your<SB>
 Rucksack that way."<SB>
"I see."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"How about the Saibara the<SB>
 blacksmith in south Mineral<SB>
 Town?<SB>
 Here you can:<SB>
 ·Upgrade tools<SB>
 ·Buy Brushes, Milkers, or<SB>
   Clippers<SB>
 ·Have Cheese, Yarn, or<SB>
   Mayonnaise Makers made<SB>
 ·Have jewelery (necklaces,<SB>
   broaches, or earrings)<SB>
   made<SB>
 Brushes, Milkers and<SB>
 Clippers are all Tools, so<SB>
 they're placed that way in<SB>
 your Rucksack.<SB>
 I'll explain the rest<SB>
 tomorrow."<SB>
"See you then."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"I was talking about<SB>
 Saibara the blacksmith,<SB>
 right? Today I'll explain<SB>
 about how to upgrade your<SB>
 Tools. First, put the Tool<SB>
 to upgrade and the Ore<SB>
 equivalent to the level you<SB>
 want to upgrade it to into<SB>
 your Rucksack. They don't<SB>
 need to be equipped."<SB>
"Which Tools can be<SB>
 upgraded?"<SB>
"Let's see...Hoe, Hammer,<SB>
 Axe, Sickle, Watering Can,<SB>
 Can, and Fishing Rod.<SB>
 Ores you can use to upgrade<SB>
 are, in order: Copper,<SB>
 Silver, Gold, and Mystrile.<SB>
 Once you've selected what<SB>
 you want, Saibara will tell<SB>
 you how much gold and time<SB>
 it will take. You can<SB>
 decide if it's worth it<SB>
 or not."<SB>
"Makes sense to me!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"I was talking about<SB>
 Saibara the blacksmith,<SB>
 right? Today I'll tell you<SB>
 more about upgrading Tools.<SB>
 Saibara's grumpy, so once<SB>
 he accepts your job, he'll<SB>
 throw you out of his shop.<SB>
 You won't be able to come<SB>
 back until he's done."<SB>
"What if I forget to go<SB>
 pick it up?"<SB>
"He won't throw it away or<SB>
 anything, but why would you<SB>
delay using your new Tool?"<SB>
"Sometimes I forget..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"I was talking about<SB>
 Saibara the blacksmith,<SB>
 right? Today I'll tell you<SB>
 about having Cheese, Yarn<SB>
 or Mayonnaise Makers made.<SB>
 First, place the necessary<SB>
 Ore in your Rucksack.<SB>
 You don't need to be<SB>
 holding it."<SB>
"Which Ore is that?"<SB>
"Adamantite. He'll tell you<SB>
 how long it takes (5 days),<SB>
 then you can confirm your<SB>
 order (or not).<SB>
 More tomorrow."<SB>
"OK."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"I was talking about having<SB>
 Saibara make you Cheese,<SB>
 Yarn, or Mayonnaise Makers,<SB>
 right?<SB>
 Once Saibara accepts your<SB>
 your job, he'll throw you<SB>
 out and get to work. You<SB>
 won't be able to go back in<SB>
 until he's done.<SB>
 But, you don't even need<SB>
 to pick it up at all.<SB>
 He'll have it delivered to<SB>
 your Barn automatically.<SB>
 Speaking of which, you<SB>
 can't buy a Maker until<SB>
 you've expanded your<SB>
Barn." "I see."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"I was talking about<SB>
 Saibara the blacksmith,<SB>
 right? Today I'll tell you<SB>
 about having Necklaces,<SB>
 Earrings, Bracelets, or<SB>
 Broaches made.<SB>
 First, place the necessary<SB>
 Ore in your Rucksack.<SB>
 You don't need to be<SB>
 holding it."<SB>
"Which Ore is that?"<SB>
"Orichalc. He'll tell you<SB>
 how long it takes (1 day),<SB>
 then you can confirm your<SB>
 order (or not).<SB>
 More tomorrow."<SB>
"OK."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"I was talking about<SB>
 ordering jewelry from<SB>
 Saibara, right?<SB>
 Saibara's grumpy, so once<SB>
 he accepts your job, he'll<SB>
 throw you out of his shop.<SB>
 You won't be able to come<SB>
 back until he's done."<SB>
"What if I forget to go<SB>
 pick it up?"<SB>
"He won't throw it away or<SB>
 anything, but there's no<SB>
 reason to let something<SB>
 so pretty go to waste..."<SB>
"You're right."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                    ADVANCED<SB>
                           <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"          <SB>
"What?"                  <SB>
"What will you teach me   <SB>
about today?"             <SB>
"How about the Aja Winery <SB>
in north Mineral Town?     <SB>
 Here you can:             <SB>
 ·Buy Wine<SB>
 ·Buy Grape Juice<SB>
 Both are food, so they'll<SB>
 go into your Rucksack as<SB>
 food Items.<SB>
 If you have a Refrigerator,<SB>
 you can buy as many as 99<SB>
 at once!"<SB>
"How many can I buy without<SB>
 a Refrigerator?"<SB>
"Only as many as you have<SB>
 room in your Rucksack for.<SB>
 You can only fit 1 per<SB>
 space, so not many."<SB>
"I see."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"How about Mary's Library<SB>
 in north Mineral Town?<SB>
 This is a great place to<SB>
 read books. And, since it's<SB>
 a Mineral Town Library,<SB>
 it has books with lots of<SB>
 useful knowledge about life<SB>
 in Mineral Town."<SB>
"Do they always have the<SB>
 same books?"<SB>
"Sometimes they get new<SB>
 books in, so I recommend<SB>
 checking every once in a<SB>
 while."<SB>
"That sounds smart."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"How about the Supermarket<SB>
 in north Mineral Town?<SB>
 Here you can:<SB>
 ·Buy Seeds<SB>
 ·Buy food<SB>
 ·Buy certain Tools<SB>
   (like Rucksacks)<SB>
 ·Have presents giftwrapped<SB>
 First, I'll talk about<SB>
 Seeds. Different Seeds are<SB>
 sold in different seasons.<SB>
 Also, they're considered<SB>
 Tools, so that's how they<SB>
 are carried in your<SB>
 Rucksack.<SB>
"Fair enough."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"I was talking about the<SB>
 Supermarket, right?"<SB>
 Today I'll tell you how to<SB>
 buy food. All the food is<SB>
 arranged by kind, so just<SB>
 investigate the kind you<SB>
 want to determine the<SB>
 amount to buy.<SB>
 You have to have space in<SB>
 your Rucksack and gold,<SB>
 of course.<SB>
 Here you can buy:<SB>
 ·Rice Balls<SB>
 ·Bread<SB>
 ·Oil<SB>
 ·Flour<SB>
 ·Curry Powder<SB>
 ·Muffin Mix<SB>
 ·Chocolate<SB>
 That's all."<SB>
"Seems like a lot to me!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"I was talking about the<SB>
 Supermarket, right?"<SB>
 First, I'll explain about<SB>
 buying Rucksacks.<SB>
 First of all, you don't<SB>
 need any room to carry<SB>
 them. As soon as you<SB>
 buy one, your space to<SB>
 carry Tools and Items will<SB>
 double.<SB>
 Also, you can only buy 1 at<SB>
 a time, and new ones may<SB>
 not come in for a while.<SB>
<SB>
 Next, I'll explain about<SB>
 Baskets. You need to have<SB>
 empty hands to buy a<SB>
 Basket, because as soon as<SB>
 you buy it, you have to<SB>
 hold it. It won't fit into<SB>
 a Rucksack, you see."<SB>
"Alright."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"I was talking about the<SB>
 Supermarket, right?"<SB>
 Today I'll talk about<SB>
 buying the Blue Feather.<SB>
 First of all, it won't go<SB>
 on sale until there's a<SB>
 girl ready to marry you."<SB>
"How do they know?"<SB>
"Everybody in Mineral Town<SB>
 knows everything about<SB>
 everybody else! Especially<SB>
 when it comes to romance."<SB>
"Sounds pretty scary to<SB>
me!" "Ha ha. By the way,<SB>
it's considered a Tool."<SB>
"OK..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"I was talking about the<SB>
 Supermarket, right?"<SB>
 Today I'll explain about<SB>
 getting gifts wrapped.<SB>
 First, place the Item you<SB>
 want to have wrapped in<SB>
 your Rucksack. You don't<SB>
 need to be holding it.<SB>
 Next, investigate the<SB>
 giftwrap counter, then<SB>
 select the Item to wrap."<SB>
"Can I have anything<SB>
 wrapped up?"<SB>
"Anything that would fit in<SB>
 a Refrigerator or Shelf."<SB>
"So no Baskets or animals.<SB>
 Got it."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"How about the Mineral<SB>
 Clinic in north Mineral<SB>
 Town?<SB>
 Here you can:<SB>
 ·Buy medicine<SB>
 ·Be examined<SB>
 To buy medicine, go talk<SB>
 to Elli behind the counter.<SB>
 In the beginning, she'll<SB>
 only sell you:<SB>
 ·Bodigizer<SB>
 ·Turbojolt<SB>
 But, if you gather lots of<SB>
 grasses growing on the<SB>
 mountain, then<SB>
 ·Bodigizer XL<SB>
 ·Turbojolt XL<SB>
 will go on sale."<SB>
"Why is that?"<SB>
"I'll explain tomorrow."<SB>
"If you say so."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"I was telling you that<SB>
 shipping grasses gathered<SB>
 on the mountain leads to<SB>
 new medicine being sold,<SB>
 right?<SB>
 That's because these<SB>
 grasses are used to make<SB>
 the medicines! Of course,<SB>
 only some kinds of grasses<SB>
 are use to make medicine."<SB>
"Could I make them, then?"<SB>
"You mean like cooking<SB>
 them up? You could try!<SB>
 Tomorrow I'll explain about<SB>
 getting examined by the<SB>
 Doctor."<SB>
"Bye for now."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"I was talking about the<SB>
 Mineral Clinic, right?<SB>
 To be examined by the<SB>
 Doctor, go talk to him<SB>
 behind his counter.<SB>
 He'll tell you exactly how<SB>
 much Stamina and Fatigue<SB>
 you have. He won't actually<SB>
 treat you, though."<SB>
"Then what good is it?"<SB>
"It's very useful to know<SB>
 exactly what kind of health<SB>
 you're in. Besides,<SB>
 it doesn't cost much."<SB>
"I guess you're right..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"How about the Doug's Inn<SB>
 in north Mineral Town?<SB>
 Here you can:<SB>
 ·Eat<SB>
 ·Make phone calls<SB>
 Doug serves different foods<SB>
 at different times of the<SB>
 day, but you can't<SB>
 take anything home."<SB>
"Some of the things Doug<SB>
 makes, I can make myself.<SB>
 Why should I pay extra<SB>
 to eat it at the Inn?"<SB>
"Doug's a pro, so his food<SB>
 will help you recuperate<SB>
 more than your own."<SB>
"Hmm..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"I was talking about the<SB>
 Doug's Inn, right?"<SB>
 Today I'll tell you about<SB>
 making phone calls.<SB>
 Just investigate the phone<SB>
 to make a call.<SB>
 The only time you'll <SB>
 need to is when ordering s<SB>
 from the TV Shopping<SB>
 Network."<SB>
"How do I know what to<SB>
 buy?" "If you see<SB>
 something on TV that you<SB>
 want, and you can<SB>
 pay for it, just go make<SB>
 the call!<SB>
 They'll deliver it after a<SB>
 set number of days."<SB>
"Sounds easy to me."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"How about the Church<SB>
 in north Mineral Town?<SB>
 Here you can:<SB>
 ·Confess<SB>
 ·Have curses lifted<SB>
 You need to go into the<SB>
 confessional inside the<SB>
 Church to do either one.<SB>
 It's door on the left.<SB>
 To confess, you'll choose<SB>
 what you want to confess<SB>
 about from a list.<SB>
 Then, Carter will tell you<SB>
 whether or not the Harvest<SB>
 Goddess will forgive you.<SB>
 If she will, you'll notice<SB>
 that townspeople like<SB>
 you more, or that your<SB>
 Stamina improves.<SB>
 Nothing bad happens if<SB>
 you're not forgiven,<SB>
 by the way."<SB>
"Seems too good<SB>
 to be true..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"Teach me more from<SB>
 yesterday!"<SB>
"I was talking about the<SB>
 Church, but I forgot to<SB>
 mention that you can only<SB>
 confess once a day.<SB>
 Today I'll explain about<SB>
 having curses lifted."<SB>
"What's a curse, sis?"<SB>
"Sometimes you'll find<SB>
 cursed Tools in the mines.<SB>
 If you equip one of these,<SB>
 you can't put it down<SB>
 until you have the curse<SB>
 lifted."<SB>
"I hope I never pick up a<SB>
 cursed Tool!"<SB>
"But, they can be very<SB>
 powerful, you know."<SB>
"I'll have to see for<SB>
 myself, I guess."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   ADVANCED<SB>
              <SB>
"Hey, big sis!"<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"What will you teach me<SB>
 about today?"<SB>
"How about the Kai's<SB>
 Seaside Lodge on Mineral<SB>
 Beach? Here you can eat<SB>
 great meals. But, just like<SB>
 Doug's Inn, you can't bring<SB>
 the leftovers home."<SB>
"Kai always serves the same<SB>
 food, right?"<SB>
"Right. The Lodge isn't<SB>
 open all that long, and<SB>
 only in the Summer,<SB>
anyway."<SB>
"It's probably worth going<SB>
 to check out, I guess."<P><END>
