Mine Research Group<SB>
                            <SB>
                            <SB>
"Good day. My name is<SB>
Karin, and I am a mine<SB>
researcher.<SB>
Today, I will tell you some<SB>
of the facts and rumors that<SB>
I have learned regarding<SB>
mines.<SB>
                            <SB>
Up to now, it had been<SB>
assumed that digging up the<SB>
ground at the Mine by the<SB>
Spring would only unearth<SB>
Gold or Black Grass.<SB>
Recently, however, the idea<SB>
that other things may be<SB>
found there has found favor<SB>
with many. One such find is<SB>
is the "Power Berry"about<SB>
which the presence of I may<SB>
claim with 100% certainty,<SB>
based on my own<SB>
investigations. It may be<SB>
found 100 levels<SB>
underground.<SB>
                            <SB>
Another is the "Mystery<SB>
Slab." While it is true,<SB>
however, that it is there to<SB>
be found, we do not know<SB>
exactly where it is located,<SB>
perhaps due to it being<SB>
buried very deep indeed. We<SB>
will inform you as soon as<SB>
we have more information<SB>
regarding this object.<SB>
That's all for this week."<P><END>
Mine Research Group<SB>
                            <SB>
                            <SB>
"Good day. My name is<SB>
Karin, and I am a mine<SB>
researcher. Today, I will<SB>
tell you some of the facts<SB>
and rumors that I have<SB>
learned regarding mines.<SB>
                            <SB>
It is known that the<SB>
following things are<SB>
comparatively common finds<SB>
when one breaks rocks at the<SB>
Mine of the Spring:<SB>
Junk Ore, Copper,<SB>
Silver, Gold, MYstrile,<SB>
Orichalch, and Adamantite.<SB>
Two more unusual objects<SB>
known to be found there,<SB>
however, are the "Teleport<SB>
Stone" and the "Goddess<SB>
Jewel." As to where<SB>
in the mine they can be<SB>
found, however, well... It<SB>
appears that our time is up<SB>
for today, so I will talk<SB>
more on this subject next<SB>
time. That's all for this<SB>
week."<P><END>
Mine Research Group<SB>
                            <SB>
                            <SB>
"Good day. My name is<SB>
Karin, and I am a mine<SB>
researcher. Today, I will<SB>
tell you some of the facts<SB>
and rumors that I have<SB>
learned regarding mines.<SB>
                            <SB>
We have learned that among<SB>
the things to be found by<SB>
breaking rocks at the Mine<SB>
of the Spring are the<SB>
Teleport Stone and the<SB>
Goddess Jewel. We believe<SB>
that the former is probably<SB>
found on the lowest level of<SB>
the mine, while the latter<SB>
is scattered here and there,<SB>
and thus, we do not know all<SB>
the places where it may be<SB>
found. We only know of two<SB>
such places at this time,<SB>
the 102nd and 202nd levels<SB>
of the mine. I will inform<SB>
you of any more information<SB>
on this subject. That's all<SB>
for this week."<P><END>
Mine Research Group<SB>
                            <SB>
                            <SB>
"Good day. My name is Karin<SB>
and I am a mine researcher.<SB>
Today, I will tell you some<SB>
of the facts and rumors that<SB>
I have learned regarding<SB>
mines.<SB>
                            <SB>
As with the Mine of the<SB>
Spring, we have found that<SB>
Power Berries can also be<SB>
found in digging at the Mine<SB>
of the Lake. My<SB>
investigations show that<SB>
they can be found on the<SB>
19th level of the Mine.<SB>
                            <SB>
Also, there have been rumors<SB>
in some quarters about<SB>
"Cursed Tools." Word now<SB>
reaches us that such tools<SB>
have been found at the Mine<SB>
of the Lake, specifically,<SB>
the Cursed Hoe, which, we<SB>
are told, was found on the<SB>
39th level of the mine. More<SB>
on this story as we get<SB>
more information. That's all<SB>
for this week."<P><END>
Mine Research Group<SB>
                            <SB>
                            <SB>
"Good day. My name is Karin<SB>
and I am a mine researcher.<SB>
Today, I will tell you some<SB>
of the facts and rumors that<SB>
I have learned regarding<SB>
mines.<SB>
                            <SB>
The following ores are known<SB>
to be found by breaking<SB>
rocks at the Mine of the<SB>
Lake: Amethyst, Agate,<SB>
Fluorite, Peridot, Topaz,<SB>
Ruby, Sand Rose,<SB>
Moonstone, Emerald, and<SB>
Diamond. Of these, the last<SB>
two are comparatively<SB>
unusual, while the others<SB>
can be found more easily.<SB>
There are, however, other<SB>
unusual things being found<SB>
in this mine... It seems,<SB>
however, that we have run<SB>
out of time, so we will<SB>
continue this discussion on<SB>
our next show, at our<SB>
leisure. Until then, that's<SB>
all for this week."<P><END>
Mine Research Group<SB>
                            <SB>
                            <SB>
"Good day. My name is Karin<SB>
and I am a mine researcher.<SB>
Today, I will tell you some<SB>
of the facts and rumors that<SB>
I have learned regarding<SB>
mines.<SB>
                            <SB>
Unusual ores that can be<SB>
found by breaking rocks at<SB>
the Mine by the Lake are<SB>
Alexandrite and Pink<SB>
Diamond. We have reports<SB>
that Alexandrite has been<SB>
found on the 50th, 100th,<SB>
150th levels of the mine,<SB>
though it may also be found<SB>
on other levels as well.<SB>
As for Pink Diamonds, we<SB>
have reports that they have<SB>
been found on the 30th,<SB>
110th, and 190th levels of<SB>
the mine, though they may<SB>
also be found on other<SB>
levels as well. We will<SB>
report further on this<SB>
subject as information<SB>
becomes available. That's<SB>
all for this week."<P><END>
Mine Research Group<SB>
                            <SB>
                            <SB>
"Good day. My name is<SB>
Karin, and I am a mine<SB>
researcher. Today, I will<SB>
tell you some of the facts<SB>
and rumors that I have<SB>
learned regarding mines.<SB>
                            <SB>
There have been rumors in<SB>
some quarters of Cursed<SB>
Tools. We have received word<SB>
that another such item has<SB>
been discovered at the Mine<SB>
by the Lake. The item in<SB>
question is a Cursed<SB>
Watering Can, and it was<SB>
found on the 69th level of<SB>
the mine. We also have<SB>
further information on<SB>
unusual things that can be<SB>
found by breaking rocks at<SB>
the Mine by the Lake. This<SB>
time, it is the Kappa Jewel,<SB>
and it appears to have been<SB>
found on the 120th level of<SB>
the mine. We do not have any<SB>
more details at this time,<SB>
though we will let you know<SB>
just as soon as we do. And<SB>
that's all for this week."<P><END>
Mine Research Group<SB>
                            <SB>
                            <SB>
"Good day. My name is<SB>
Karin, and I am a mine<SB>
researcher. Today, I will<SB>
tell you some of the facts<SB>
and rumors that I have<SB>
learned regarding mines.<SB>
                            <SB>
Lately, the rumor has been<SB>
circulating that if you<SB>
charge when using your<SB>
hoe or hammer at<SB>
the mines, you will find<SB>
more items. This is an<SB>
absolute lie, however, so do<SB>
not waste your energies in<SB>
this futile undertaking.<SB>
                            <SB>
Next, we have a report of<SB>
Alexandrite having been<SB>
found on the 210th level of<SB>
the Mine of the Lake. If<SB>
anyone else out there has<SB>
news in this regard, please<SB>
let us know. And that is all<SB>
for this week."<P><END>
Mine Research Group<SB>
                            <SB>
                            <SB>
"Good day. My name is<SB>
Karin, and I am a mine<SB>
researcher. Today, I will<SB>
tell you some of the facts<SB>
and rumors that I have<SB>
learned regarding mines.<SB>
                            <SB>
Lately, a rumor has been<SB>
spreading about the mines<SB>
extending as far as 255<SB>
levels. While we are doing<SB>
our best to find an answer<SB>
to this claim, we have only<SB>
been down as far as the<SB>
255th level a very few<SB>
times, and while we cannot<SB>
say for certain, we have not<SB>
found a stairway down to the<SB>
255th level. It would not<SB>
surprise us to learn that<SB>
that was the lowest level<SB>
after all.<SB>
                            <SB>
We also have additional<SB>
information about the<SB>
finding of the Kappa Jewel<SB>
in the Mine by the Lake,<SB>
this time on the 60th level.<SB>
If you have any other such<SB>
information, please let us<SB>
know. And that's all for<SB>
this week."<P><END>
Mine Research Group<SB>
                            <SB>
                            <SB>
"Good day. My name is<SB>
Karin, and I am a mine<SB>
researcher. Today, I will<SB>
tell you some of the facts<SB>
and rumors that I have<SB>
learned regarding mines.<SB>
                            <SB>
Lately, we have heard rumors<SB>
that it is possible to go to<SB>
the Mine by the Lake in<SB>
seasons other than Winter.<SB>
The short answer is that it<SB>
is indeed possible, and easy<SB>
to do. All you have to do is<SB>
ready a Teleport, and<SB>
set the Mine by the Lake as<SB>
your destination. While this<SB>
may sound simple, actually<SB>
acquiring a Teleport<SB>
is considered quite<SB>
difficult. I have used it<SB>
myself to go to the Mine by<SB>
the Lake in seasons other<SB>
than Winter, and did not see<SB>
any particular difference. I<SB>
will report again on this<SB>
subject as further<SB>
information becomes<SB>
available. That's all for<SB>
this week."<P><END>
Mine Research Group<SB>
                            <SB>
                            <SB>
"Good day. My name is<SB>
Karin, and I am a mine<SB>
researcher. Today, I will<SB>
tell you some of the facts<SB>
and rumors that I have<SB>
learned regarding mines.<SB>
                            <SB>
First of all, word comes to<SB>
us today of the discovery of<SB>
the Goddess Jewel,<SB>
on the 152nd level of the<SB>
Mine of the Spring.<SB>
                            <SB>
We have another report of<SB>
the Goddess Jewel<SB>
being found in that Mine,<SB>
this time on the 190th<SB>
level.<SB>
                            <SB>
Next, we have word of a<SB>
Cursed Sickle being found in<SB>
the Mine by the Lake, on the<SB>
79th level. And that<SB>
concludes today's report.<SB>
Please let us know if you<SB>
have any other information<SB>
in this regard. And that's<SB>
all for this week."<P><END>
Mine Research Group<SB>
                            <SB>
                            <SB>
"Good day. My name is<SB>
Karin, and I am a mine<SB>
researcher. Today, I will<SB>
tell you some of the facts<SB>
and rumors that I have<SB>
learned regarding mines.<SB>
                            <SB>
Lately, we have been hearing<SB>
rumors that sowing seeds in<SB>
mine land after it has been<SB>
dug up will cause even<SB>
seasonal plants to grow.<SB>
This is completely untrue,<SB>
however, so do not waste<SB>
your seeds in this fruitless<SB>
pursuit.<SB>
                            <SB>
Next, we have news of Pink<SB>
Diamond being found, on the<SB>
90th level of the Mine of<SB>
the Lake. And that concludes<SB>
today's report. If you have<SB>
any other information,<SB>
please let us know. And<SB>
that's all for this week."<P><END>
Mine Research Group<SB>
                            <SB>
                            <SB>
"Good day. My name is<SB>
Karin, and I am a mine<SB>
researcher. Today, I will<SB>
tell you some of the facts<SB>
and rumors that I have<SB>
learned regarding mines.<SB>
                            <SB>
The other day, I apparently<SB>
discovered something<SB>
amazing. On the 222nd level<SB>
of the Mine by the Spring, I<SB>
found a Mythic Stone, an ore<SB>
that I had never before<SB>
found, when I was breaking<SB>
rocks. As this was my first<SB>
such discovery, I am not<SB>
sure just how I found it. If<SB>
any of you have any<SB>
information about the Mythic<SB>
Stone, or anything else, for<SB>
that matter, please let us<SB>
know. Thank you. And that's<SB>
all for this week."<P><END>
