Goo-goo.<P><END>
Yes<END>
No<END>
You think this meal is different from what I usually cook?<P><C>
That's because today is special! Do you know why?<P><END>
Our anniversary<END>
My birthday<END>
Your birthday<END>
...Our anniversary? You were just kidding, right? I hope you'd<WB>
remember your own birthday!<P><END>
I'd better apologize later...<P><END>
Happy birthday! Are you surprised?<P><END>
I can't wait to have a baby. I love kids.<P><END>
I had so much fun today! I'll sleep like a log...<P><END>
Well, maybe I shouldn't expect you to remember MY birthday, but at least <WB>
remember your OWN!<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO6>'s birthday<END>
Now you're a year older and a dad as well, so it's time to stop goofing around!<P><END>
You really are a strange one, aren't you?<P><C>
How many people forget both their own and their child's birthday...?<P><END>
Hurry up and finish. Today is an important day.<P><END>
