Goo-goo.<P><END>
Yes<END>
No<END>
You know what day it is today, right...?<P><END>
Our anniversary<END>
My birthday<END>
Your birthday<END>
Sorry, try again. It's your own birthday! Are you pulling my leg?<P><END>
I'd better apologize later...<P><END>
That's right! You're getting older now, so you have more responsibilities, too!<P><END>
Sorry all my food is the same as at the Inn.<P><C>
I learned it all from dad!<P><END>
I had so much fun today! I'll sleep like a log...<P><END>
My birthday!?... Get a grip! It's YOUR birthday!<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO6>'s birthday<END>
Stop fooling me! I know you know it's your own birthday!<P><END>
Hurry up and finish. Today is an important day.<P><END>
