Are you done with work?<P><END>
Yes<END>
No<END>
Looks good, doesn't it? It's a special meal for a special day! Know why?<P><END>
Our anniversary<END>
My birthday<END>
Your birthday<END>
Hmm...It's even more important to me than our anniversary.<P><C>
It's your birthday, silly!<P><END>
I'd better apologize later...<P><END>
Happy birthday! Let's have a glass of wine to celebrate!<P><END>
Well, we will celebrate our anniversaries just like this...Forever!<P><END>
I had so much fun today! I'll sleep like a log...<P><END>
Ha ha ha! I can't believe you mixed up our birthdays! You sure are <WB>
cute, <NAME_MEMO2>.<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO6>'s birthday<END>
That's right! Let's spend the night celebrating!<P><END>
Well, we will celebrate our family anniversaries just  like this...Forever!<P><END>
Ha ha ha! I can't believe you mixed up your birthday with <WB>
<NAME_MEMO6>'s!<P><C>
You sure are cute!<P><END>
Hurry up and finish. Today is an important day.<P><END>
