Are you done with work?<P><END>
Yes<END>
No<END>
I don't usually bake cakes, but surely you know why I did today, right?<P><END>
It's my birthday.<END>
It's your birthday.<END>
<NAME_MEMO6>'s birthday.<END>
Are you becoming senile already...? I hope not!<P><C>
It's <NAME_MEMO6>'s birthday, silly!<P><END>
I'd better apologize later...<P><END>
I'm flattered you're thinking of me, but it's <WB>
your son's birthday, not mine, silly!<P><END>
Of course you remember <NAME_MEMO6>'s birthday! Who could forget their own<WB>
son's birthday!<P><END>
I enjoy watching him grow up, don't you?<P><END>
I had so much fun today! I'll sleep like a log...<P><END>
Hurry up and finish. Today is an important day.<P><END>
