Are you done with work?<P><END>
Yes<END>
No<END>
Doesn't this cake look good? You know why I baked it, right?<P><END>
My birthday.<END>
Your birthday.<END>
<NAME_MEMO6>'s birthday.<END>
I can't believe you would confuse your own birthday with your son's!<P><C>
You really are funny, <NAME_MEMO2>.<P><END>
I'd better apologize later...<P><END>
Thanks for thinking about me, but aren't you forgetting <NAME_MEMO6>?<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO6> is lucky to have such a considerate father!<P><END>
I can't wait until he grows up and we can go out on the town together!<P><C>
His father sure won't take me...<P><END>
I had so much fun today! I'll sleep like a log...<P><END>
Hurry up and finish. Today is an important day.<P><END>
