Good morning!! Do you know what makes today special?<P><END>
Your birthday<END>
Our anniversary<END>
My birthday<END>
My birthday? No, it's our anniversary, silly! I can't believe you <WB>
forgot! I could hardly wait to give you a present!<P><C>
I'm not giving it to someone so thoughtless!<P><END>
You're right! I was afraid you'd forget, but you are so wonderful <WB>
you always surprise me!<P><C>
I love you, <NAME_MEMO2>!<P><END>
Here you are, <NAME_MEMO2>.<P><END>
I'm going to give you a present, so empty your hands, OK?<P><END>
Your kidding, aren't you?! Do you have a fever, because if you don't <WB>
there's no excuse for this!<P><C>
It's our anniversary, silly!<P><END>
