Good morning, <NAME_MEMO2>. Sleep well? Do you know what today is?<P><END>
Your birthday<END>
Our anniversary<END>
My birthday<END>
My birthday? No, it's our anniversary, silly! I can't believe you <WB>
forgot! I could hardly wait to give you a present!<P><C>
Well, I'm not giving it to you any more!<P><END>
You're right! You're such a sweet husband!<P><C>
I knew you wouldn't forget! Here's a present!<P><END>
Here you are, <NAME_MEMO2>.<P><END>
I'm going to give you a present, so empty your hands, OK?<P><END>
Is that a joke!? I can't believe how self-centered you are!<P><C>
I was going to give you a gift, but not any more!<P><END>
