I think I might have come down with something...<P><C>
I feel sick to my stomach.<P><C>
<NAME_MEMO2>, will you take me to the Clinic?<P><END>
Thanks. You're a sweetheart.<P><END>
Your wife isn't sick.<P><END>
You're going to be parents. Congratulations!<P><END>
Congratulations, Elli. You always did want a baby.<P><END>
I...I understand.<P><END>
I can't believe I'm actually pregnant!<P><END>
I can't wait to tell Grandma and everybody! Let's go home!<P><END>
I can't believe I'm about to become a father... This is so great!<P><END>
