Are you done with work?<P><END>
Yes<END>
No<END>
Does this remind you of something?<P><END>
Our anniversary<END>
My birthday<END>
Your birthday<END>
Our anniversary, huh?<P><C>
In that case...just when do you think my birthday is!?<P><END>
I'd better apologize later...<P><END>
Ha! Sometimes you really are like a character in a story! It's my birthday, silly!<P><END>
That's right. Today I'm a year older, and hopefully a year wiser.<P><END>
It's no fun having your birthday be the same day as your parents' anniversary!<P><END>
I had so much fun today! I'll sleep like a log...<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO6>'s birthday<END>
Ha! Sometimes you really are like a character in a story! It's my birthday, silly<P><END>
What kind of a father doesn't know his own son's or his own wife's birthday?!<P><C>
Today is MY birthday!<P><END>
Hurry up and finish. Today is an important day.<P><END>
