I don't look so good... I shouldn't work today. Get some rest instead.<P><END>
I don't look so good... Better eat something to help me recuperate<WB>
from Fatigue.<P><END>
It's already late. I should get to bed.<P><END>
Co le la gan sang roi...  Bay gio minh nen di ngu mot chut... <P><END>
It's getting late. I'd better go to bed.<P><END>
Night <P><END>
Midnight <P><END>
Another day to enjoy!<P><END>
Morning <P><END>
It's still noon. I should get back to work.<P><END>
Noon <P><END>
It's still evening. I should get back to work.<P><END>
Evening <P><END>
It's getting dark, so I should finish up my work.<P><END>
Almost nighttime. <P><END>
It's dark already, so I should quit working.<P><END>
My Fatigue builds up more easily in bad weather, but working this late will tire<WB>
me out even faster!<P><END>
When I use your Tools in bad weather, I build up Fatigue faster, so <WB>
be careful.<P><END>
I can't go outside in a Typhoon. Get some extra sleep.<P><END>
The winds outside are practically a gale. I hope the House can take this.<P><END>
I can't go outside in so much snow. Get some extra sleep.<P><END>
