You forgot to bring  lunch along today, didn't you? Here it is.<P><END>
Thanks! Sorry to trouble you.<P><END>
It's no trouble at all.<P><END>
Hi, Ann. Welcome.<P><END>
Sorry to bug you, Duke.<P><END>
What's your errand?<P><END>
I forgot my lunch, so Ann brought it for me.<P><END>
That's nice of you, Ann. You two are almost like an old married couple!<P><END>
..........<P><END>
Duke!<P><END>
What?...<P><END>
I'll be getting back, now. Bye.<P><END>
Ann! Wait...<P><END>
She likes you...I can tell. You like her, too, right?<P><C>
Why bother waiting? You could go propose to her right now, if you wanted...<P><END>
Wh-what are you talking about!?...<P><END>
You're like my own son, you know.<P><C>
I think Ann and you would make a good couple.<P><END>
