Cough...cough...<P><END>
Doctor, are you alright?<P><END>
I'm fine...<P><END>
Why don't you take the day off?<P><END>
I could never let down the people who need me!<P><END>
But...<P><END>
Don't worry about me. I know how to take care of myself.<P><C>
Besides, I have you with me.<P><END>
If you say so, Doctor. Just don't overdo it!<P><END>
If you do, I'll get mad at you!<P><END>
Ha ha! You sound like my mother, you know.<P><END>
You'll be a good wife to somebody, Elli.<P><END>
Are you teasing me...?<P><END>
