Popuri and I are thinking of moving to another town...<P><END>
Is this true?! Popuri!<P><END>
...It is.<P><END>
Really...? What'll I do...<P><END>
I tried to convince her to stay.<P><END>
Liar! I bet you are the one who's trying to take her!<P><END>
It's not Kai's fault. It really was my idea.<P><END>
I won't allow it!<P><END>
We're going no matter what!<P><END>
It's OK. I don't mind.<P><END>
...M-mom! What are you saying?<P><END>
Really! Fantastic!<P><END>
If that's what they really want to do, then I don't want to stop them.<P><END>
I have a condition, though. Kai, you must make Popuri happy forever!<P><END>
Mom!...<P><END>
Wha... What is this all of a sudden?<P><END>
You don't have to answer now. Just think about it.<P><END>
.....I'll go home and think about it.<P><END>
